原創翻譯  雙語字幕
僅供學習 禁止用於任何商業盈利行為
更多影視更新
請登陸www.ZiMuZu.tv
翻譯：somehacker 杏仁斯嘉麗 木淺 x6324
翻譯：小英的小號 小蠻腰
時間軸：獅市長Ans 羊副市長路帕斯 尼克浪浪
時間軸：閃電Jessie 豹警官Meng 牛局長姜姜
校對：somehacker
後期：吉吉     總監：somehacker
瘋狂動物城
恐懼  背叛和嗜血
Fear, treachery, blood lust.
數萬年前支配著我們的世界
Thousands of years ago these were the forces that ruled our world
那時食草動物懼怕食肉動物
A world where prey were scared of predators.
而食肉動物無法遏制的本能
And predators had an uncontrollable...
讓他們捕獵  殘殺  還有
biological urge to maim, and maul, and...
流血  血  血
Blood! Blood! Blood!
和死亡
And.. Death!
那時世界分成兩部分
Back then, the world was divided in two.
凶殘的食肉動物  和溫順的食草動物
Vicious predator, or meek prey.
凶殘的食肉動物
溫順的食草動物
但我們也隨著時間進化
But over time, we evolved,
將這原始野蠻的生活方式拋在身後
and moved beyond or primitive savage ways.
現在食肉和食草動物和諧共處
Now predator and prey live in harmony.
每隻哺乳動物的未來都有了無限可能
And every young mammal has multitudinous opportunities.
我不用再縮在羊群裡了
Yeah, I don't have to cower in a a herd anymore.
英文的黑羊Black Sheep等於中文的害群之馬
我可以做宇航員
Instead, I can be an astronaut.
我不用再孤單地追捕狩獵了
I don't have to be a lonely hunter anymore.
我可以追捕逃稅的人
Today I can hunt for tax exemptions.
我要做精算師
I'm gonna be an actuary.
我可以讓世界更美好  我要做
And I can make the world a better place. I am going to be...
警察
A police officer!
兔子警察  簡直蠢透了
Bunny cop? That is the most stupidest thing I ever heard!
眼界狹窄的當然覺得不可能
It may seem impossible to small minds.
說的就是你  吉迪恩·格雷
I'm looking at you, Gideon Grey.
但是211英里外就是偉大的動物城
But, just 211 miles away, stands the great city of Zootopia.
我們雙方的祖先簽訂和平契約
Where our ancestors first joined together in peace.
胡蘿蔔日才藝秀
正式宣佈  誰都能成就無限可能
And declared that anyone can be anything!
謝謝大家  晚安
Thank you and good night.
朱迪  你想沒想過
Judy, you ever wonder how
你媽媽和我為什麼這麼幸福嗎
your mom and me got to be so darn happy?
沒有
Nope.
我們放棄了夢想  安定了下來  對嗎邦妮
Well, we gave up on our dreams, and we settled. Right, Bon?
是啊  斯圖  我們可安定了
Oh, yes. That's right, Stu. We settled hard.
這就是知足常樂  朱迪
You see, that's the beauty of complacency, Jude.
不嘗試新的事物  就絕不會失敗
If you don't try anything new, you'll never fail.
我挺喜歡嘗試的
I like trying, actually.
親愛的  你爸爸是說
What your father means, hon,
成為警官對你來說非常難
is that it's gonna be difficult, impossible even...
甚至是不可能的
for you to become a police officer.
是啊  還從沒有兔子做過警察
Right. There's never been a bunny cop.
-沒有  -兔子不做警察
- No. - Bunnies don't do that.
-絕不會  -絕不
- Never. - Never.
那我就是第一個了
Well... Then I guess I'll have to be the first one.
因為我要讓世界更美好
Because I am gonna make the world a better place!
或者  這樣
Or, heck, you know.
想讓世界更美好嗎
You wanna talk about making the world a better place,
做個種胡蘿蔔的農民最好了
no better way to do it than becoming a carrot farmer.
是啊  你爸爸和我  還有你275個兄弟姐妹
Yes! Your dad, me, your 275 brothers and sisters.
我們就是在改變世界
We're changing the world.
-一根胡蘿蔔一根胡蘿蔔地拯救  -可不是嘛
- One carrot at a time. - Amen to that.
種胡蘿蔔是光榮的職業
Carrot farming is a noble profession.
只要把種子
Just pulling their seeds out
撒進土裡
And one with the soil...
懂嗎  有夢想是好事
You get it, honey? I mean, it's great to have dreams.
只要別陷進去就好
Yeah, just as long as you don't believe in them too much.
她去哪了
Where the heck'd she go?
把票給我
Give me your tickets right now,
不然揍扁你溫順的小屁股
or I'm gonna kick your meek little sheep butt.
住手  吉迪恩
Cut it out, Gideon!
咩咩  你要哭嗎
Baah, baah! What are you gonna do, cry?
-聽她的  快住手  -戲服不錯  小廢物
- You heard her. Cut it out. - Nice costume, loser.
你是活在什麼地方
What crazy world are you living in
覺得兔子能當警察嗎
where you think a bunny could be a cop?
乖乖把票還給他們
Kindly return my friend's tickets.
有種來拿  但是小心點
Come and get them. But watch out.
因為我是狐狸
Cause I'm a fox,
你在那蠢貨舞台劇上野說了
and like you said in your dumb little stage play,
以前食肉動物吃食草動物
us predators used to eat prey.
殺手本能還在我們的DANA裡
And that killer instinct's still in our DANA.
那個  應該是DNA
Uh, I'm pretty much sure it's pronounced DNA.
我知道  不用你告訴我  崔維斯
Don't tell me what I know, Travis.
我不怕你  吉迪恩
You don't scare me, Gideon.
現在怕了嗎
Scared now?
看那鼻子抽的  她怕了呢
Look at her nose twitch, she is scared.
哭吧  小兔兔  哭吧
Cry, little baby bunny! Cry...
你就是不肯放棄是吧
Oh, you don't know when to quit, do you?
你給我記住這一刻
I want you to remember this moment
免得你再不安分
the next time you think you will ever be...
忘了自己就是只種胡蘿蔔的蠢兔子
anything more than just a stupid carrot-farming dumb bunny.
-好重啊  -你沒事吧  朱迪
- That looks bad. - Are you okay, Judy?
我沒事  給你
Yeah, yeah, I'm okay. Here you go.
-你把票拿回來了  -你真棒  朱迪
- Wow, you got our tickets! - You're awesome, Judy.
吉迪恩·格雷真是胡說八道
Yeah, that Gideon Grey doesn't know what he's talking about!
有件事他是說對了
Well, he was right about one thing.
我就是不肯放棄
I don't know when to quit.
動物城警官學校
聽好了  菜鳥們
Listen up, cadets.
動物城境內有12個獨特的生態系統
Zootopia has 12 unique ecosystems within its city limits.
15年後
比如冰原鎮  撒哈拉廣場  熱帶雨林區
Tundratown, Sahara Square, Rainforest District, to name a few.
正式上崗前
You're gonna have to
每個區域都要非常熟悉
master all of them before you hit the streets.
不然呢  就死了
Or guess what? You'll be dead!
熾熱沙塵暴
Scorching sandstorm.
死了  兔寶寶
You're dead, bunny bumpkin.
一千英尺攀高
One thousand foot fall.
死了  胡蘿蔔頭
You're dead, carrot face.
冰牆攀巖
Frigid ice wall.
死了  小山妞
You're dead, farm girl.
大塊頭罪犯  死了
Enormous criminal. You're dead.
死了  死了  死了
Dead. Dead. Dead.
髒馬桶  死了  小毛球
Filthy toilet. You're dead, fluff butt.
退學回家吧  毛兔兔
Just quit and go home, fuzzy bunny.
-從沒有兔子當過警察  -從沒有
There's never been a bunny cop. - Never.
-從沒有  -種胡蘿蔔的蠢兔子
- Never. - Just a stupid carrot-farming dumb bunny.
作為動物城的市長
As mayor of Zootopia,
我很榮幸地宣佈  哺乳動物選拔行動的
I am proud to announce that my mammal inclusion initiative,
第一批警校學員已經畢業了
has produced its first police academy graduate.
本屆畢業生代表  警校第一位兔子警官
Valedictorian of her class, ZPD's very first rabbit officer...
朱迪·霍普斯
Judy Hopps.
頭羊市長助理  她的警徽
Assistant Mayor Bellwether, her badge.
-對了  -謝謝
- Oh, yes, yes! - Thank you.
朱迪  我很榮幸地
Judy, it is my great privilege
將你分配到動物城的中心
to officially assign you to the heart of Zootopia...
一區  市中心
Precinct One. City Center.
恭喜你  霍普斯警官
Congratulations, Officer Hopps.
我不會讓你失望的
I won't let you down.
這是我從小的夢想
This has been my dream since I was a kid.
這是屬於我們小動物的驕傲
You know, it's a real proud day for us little guys.
頭羊  快點讓開
Bellwether, make room, will you? Come on.
好了  霍普斯警官  笑一個
Okay, Officer Hopps. Let's see those teeth!
霍普斯警官  看這裡
Officer Hopps, look here.
-我們真為你驕傲  朱迪  -也有點擔心
- We're real proud of you, Judy. - Yeah, and scared too.
-是啊  -又驕傲又擔心
- Yes. - Really, it's kind of a proud-scared combo.
動物城啊  那麼遠  那麼大
I mean, Zootopia. So far away, such a big city.
爸媽  我這輩子都在為這一刻努力
Guys, I've been working for this my whole life.
我們知道  我們是替你高興  也有點害怕
We know. And we're just a little excited for you, but terrified.
除了恐懼  沒什麼好害怕的
The only thing we have to fear is fear itself.
還有熊  熊也要怕
And also bears. We have bears to fear, too.
-更不用說獅子和狼了  -狼
- Say nothing on lions, and wolves. - Wolves?
-黃鼠狼  -你還和黃鼠狼玩過牌
- Weasels. - You played cribbage with a weasel once?
是啊  他那作弊真是沒底線
Yeah, he cheats like there's no tomorrow.
說真的  食肉動物都一樣
You know what? Pretty much all predators.
-動物城全都是  -斯圖
- And Zootopia is full of them. - Oh, Stu.
狐狸是最差勁的
And foxes are the worst.
你爸爸說的有點道理
Yeah, actually, your father does have a point there.
這是天生的  還記得吉迪恩·格雷嗎
It's in their biology. Remember what happened with Gideon Grey?
我才九歲  他是個混蛋  剛好也是隻狐狸
When I was nine. Gideon Grey was a jerk who happens to be a fox.
我認識的兔子裡也有不少混蛋呢
I know plenty of bunnies who are jerks.
是啊  可不是  可是以防萬一
Sure, yeah, we all do, absolutely. But just in case,
我們給你弄了個愛心包
we made you a little care package to take with you.
-放了點點心  -這是震狐器
- I put some snacks in there. - This is fox deterrent.
-拿著挺放心的  -驅狐噴霧
- Yeah, it's safe to have that. - This is fox repellant.
又震懾又驅趕  夠了
The deterrent and the repellant, that's all she needs.
-看看這個  -天哪
- Check this out! - Oh, for goodness sake!
不用帶電狐器吧  斯圖
She has no need for a fox taser, Stu.
得了吧  電狐器總能用得上
Oh, come on. When is there not a need for a fox taser?
好了  好吧  我帶著這個  好讓你們消停
Well, okay, look, I will take this... To make you stop talking.
太棒了  大家都開心
Terrific! Everyone wins!
進站列車  終點動物城
Arriving, Zootopia Express.
好了  得走了  再見
Okay, gotta go. Bye!
我愛你們
I love you, guys.
愛你
Love you, too.
天哪  要哭鼻子了
Oh, cripes, here come the waterworks.
斯圖  振作點
Oh, Stu. Pull it together.
大家再見
Bye everybody!
再見  朱迪  我愛你
Bye Judy, I love you! Bye!
再見
Bye!
正駛離兔窩鎮
人口
夏奇羚
動物城
我是夏奇羚  歡迎來到動物城
I'm Gazelle. Welcome to Zootopia.
歡迎來到穿山甲公寓
And welcome to the Grand Pangolin Arms.
魅力四射的豪華公寓
Luxury apartments with charm.
每月一次免費除虱  鑰匙別丟了
Complementary delousing once a month. Don't lose your key!
謝謝
Thank you.
-你們好  我是朱迪  新鄰居  -我們聲音可大了
- Oh, hi! I'm Judy, your new neighbour! - Yeah? Well, we're loud.
也不會道歉的
Don't expect us to apologize for it.
油油的牆
Greasy walls.
晃晃的床
Rickety bed.
瘋癲的鄰居
Crazy neighbors.
我喜歡
I love it!
別這樣  他先露的牙
Come on! He bared his teeth first!
你好
Excuse me!
在下面
Down here!
-你好  -我的天哪
- Hi. - O... M... Goodness!
還真找了隻兔子啊
They really did hire a bunny.
天哪  說實話
Ho-whop! I gotta tell you,
你比我想的還要可愛
you're even cuter than I thought you'd be.
你可能不知道
Ooh, ah, you probably didn't know,
兔子可以互相說可愛
but a bunny can call another bunny "Cute",
但是換了其他動物  就有點...
but when other animals do it, that's a little...
真抱歉  我  本傑明·爪豪斯
I am so sorry! Me, Benjamin Clawhauser.
大家都以為我
The guy everyone thinks is
只是愛吃甜甜圈的軟萌警察  還給你套刻板印象
just a flabby donut-loving cop, stereotyping you.
沒事的
No, it's okay.
你那裡有個  那個
You've actually got... there's a...
-什麼  -脖子裡  領子上面
- A what? - In your neck. The fold.
-那個  -你在這啊  小壞蛋
- The... this... - Oh, there you went, you little dickens!
我得去點名了  哪邊...
Hehehe, I should get to roll call, so which way do I...
-候補區在那邊左側  -謝謝
- Oh, bull pen's over there to the left. - Great. Thank you!
這小兔子會被生吞活剝的
That poor little bunny's gonna get eaten alive.
我是霍普斯警官  準備好讓世界更美好了嗎
Officer Hopps. You ready to make the world a better place?
全體都有
Attention!
好了  好了  都坐下
All right. All right. Everybody sit.
我這裡有三件事
I've got three items on the docket.
首先來說屋子裡的大象
First, we need to acknowledge the elephant in the room.
顯而易見的事
弗朗辛  生日快樂
Francine. Happy birthday.
第二件事
Number two.
有些新人我得介紹一下
There are some new recruits with us I should introduce,
我就不介紹了  因為  我不在乎
but I'm not going to because... I don't care.
最後  有14起哺乳動物失蹤案
Finally, we have 14 missing mammal cases.
全是食肉動物  從大北極熊到小水獺
All predators. From a giant polar bear to a teensy little otter.
市政廳天天追在我屁股後面
And City Hall is right up my tail to find them.
這是頭等大事  任務分配
This is priority number one. Assignments.
灰熊利  牙邁爾  德爾加多警官
Officers Grizzoli, Fangmeyer, Delgato.
你們負責熱帶雨林區的失蹤案
Your team take missing mammals from the Rainforest District.
麥克角  犀威茲  狼法德警官
Officers McHorn, Rhinowitz, Wolfard.
你們負責撒哈拉廣場區
Your teams take Sahara Square.
河馬金斯  吼洛夫  象克鼻警官  冰原鎮
Officers Higgins, Snarlov, Trunkaby. Tundratown.
最後  第一隻兔子  霍普斯警官
And finally, our first bunny, Officer Hopps.
交通協管  解散
Parking duty. Dismissed.
交通協管
Parking duty?
局長  牛局長
Chief? Chief Bogo?
長官  你說有14起哺乳動物失蹤案
Sir. You said there were fourteen missing mammal cases.
-所以呢  -我可以負責一起
- So? - So I can handle one.
您可能忘了  我畢業時是班裡第一名
You probably forgot but, I was top of my class at the academy.
沒忘  就是不在乎
Didn't forget. Just don't care.
長官  我可不是只吉祥物
Sir, I'm not just some token bunny.
那一天開100張停車罰單應該沒問題
Well then, writing a hundred tickets a day should be easy.
100張  我才不開100張呢
100 tickets. I'm not gonna write 100 tickets.
我要開200張  中午之前
I'm gonna write 200 tickets. Before noon.
隨時停車
中午之前200張
Two hundred tickets before noon!
201張
201.
看著點路  狐狸
Hey, watch where you're going, fox!
他去哪了
Where'd he go?
我不知道你大白天的
Listen. I know what you're doing
出來晃悠什麼呢
skulking around during daylight hours,
但我不想惹麻煩  快走吧
but I don't want any trouble in here. So hit the road!
我也不是想找麻煩的
I'm not looking for any trouble either, sir...
我只想買個大冰棍  給我兒子
I simply wanna buy a Jumbo-Pop. For my little boy.
要紅的還是藍的
You want the red, or the blue, pal?
我真是
I'm such a...
行了  孩子  回去吧
Oh, come on, kid. Back up.
-聽我說  -怎麼了
- Listen, buddy. - What?
你那邊沒有給狐狸開的冰淇淋店嗎
There aren't any fox ice cream joints in your part of town?
有啊  有  只是我兒子
No, no. There are, there are. It's just, my boy,
這隻小傻狐狸  特別迷大象
this goofy little stinker, he loves all things elephant.
長大了也想當大象
He wants to be one when he grows up.
多可愛啊
Isn't that adorable?
我怎麼忍心讓他夢想破滅呢
Who the heck am I to crush his little dreams, huh? Right?
你是不識字嗎  狐狸  看這個
Look, you probably can't read, fox, but the sign says
我們有權拒絕提供服務
we reserve the right to refuse service to anyone!
快走吧
So beat it.
後面都等著呢
You're holding up the line.
你好  不好意思
Hello. Excuse me.
你也和其他人一樣
Hey, you're gonna have to
得排隊等著  交通協管
wait your turn like everyone else, meter maid.
其實我是警員
Actually, I'm an officer.
就問一下
Just have a quick question.
你的顧客們知道
Are your customers aware they're getting
吃的餅乾和冰淇淋裡有鼻涕嗎
snot and mucus with their cookies and cream?
你說什麼呢
What are you talking about?
我不想惹麻煩
Well. I don't wanna cause you any trouble,
但是不戴鼻套盛冰淇淋
but I believe scooping ice cream with
是嚴重違反健康條例的
an ungloved trunk is a class 3 health code violation.
這也不是小事了
Which is kind of a big deal.
當然  如果你肯戴上
Of course I could let you off
我是可以給你個警告了事
with a warning if you were to glove those trunks
而且  還得給這位
and... I don't know... finish selling this...
爸爸和他兒子  賣一根  什麼
nice dad and his son a... What was it?
大冰棒  拜託了
A Jumbo-Pop. Please.
大冰棒
A Jumbo-Pop.
-15塊  -非常感謝  謝謝你
- $15. - Thank you so much. Thank you.
不會吧
Oh no, are you kidding me...
忘帶錢包了
I don't have my wallet!
真是就差忘帶腦袋了
I'd lose my head if it weren't attached to my neck.
真是啊  天哪  不好意思
That's the truth. Oh, boy. I'm sorry, pal.
大概是你最糟的生日了
Gotta be about the worst birthday ever.
別生我的氣  謝謝你
Please don't be mad at me. Thanks anyway.
不用找了
Keep the change.
警官  真是感恩戴德
Officer, I can't thank you enough.
太好了  怎麼回報你啊
So kind. Really. Can I pay you back?
不用  我請了
Oh, no. My treat.
主要是聽到別人
It's just, you know it burns me up
對狐狸有偏見我就受不了
to see folks with such backward attitudes towards foxes.
我只是想說
I just want to say you're
你是位好父親  口才真棒
a great dad and just a real articulate fella.
真是過獎了
Well, that is high praise.
我也很少遇到不看低我的人
It's rare that I find someone so non-patronizing.
-警官你叫  -霍普斯  你是
- Officer? - Hopps. Mr..?
王爾德  尼克·王爾德
Wilde. Nick Wilde.
你呢  小傢伙  長大了想做大象嗎
And you, little guy. You wanna be an elephant when you grow up?
那就去做大象好了  這是動物城
You be an elephant. Because this is Zootopia.
誰都能成就無限可能
Anyone can be anything.
我總這麼跟他說
I tell him that all the time.
好了  給你  雙爪抱住
All right, here you go. Two paws.
看這笑臉  生日快樂真開心
Yeah. Oh, look at that smile, that's a happy birthday smile!
好了  嘟嘟兩聲道個別吧
All right, give her a little bye-bye toot-toot.
-再見了  -再見
- Bye, now! - Goodbye!
小大象
Hey, little toot-toot...
鼠曼兄弟銀行
爪子冰棍
Pawpsicles.
來吃爪子冰棍
Get your Pawpsicles.
爪子冰棍
-木材送到了  -怎麼這個顏色
- Lumber delivery. - What's with the color?
顏色  這是紅木
The color? Uh... it's redwood.
39, 40, there you go.
裝小孩真厲害  大傢伙
Way to work that diaper, big guy.
不跟爸爸吻別嗎
No kiss bye-bye for daddy?
再敢親我  我把你臉咬下來
You kiss me tomorrow, I'll bite your face off!
再見
Ciao.
我為你出頭  你卻騙了我
Well, I stood up for you, and you lied to me.
騙子
You liar!
這叫智取  親愛的
It's called a hustle, Sweetheart.
我可不是騙子  他才是
And I'm not the liar. He is.
好了  狡猾的尼克  你被捕了
All right, Slick-Nick. You're under arrest.
真的嗎  為什麼
Really? For what?
我也不清楚  無證經營食品嗎
Gee, I don't know. How about selling food without a permit?
跨區運輸未申報商品
Transporting undeclared commerce across borough lines?
-虛假廣告  -許可證  商品申報憑證
- False advertizing. - Permit. Receipt of declared commerce.
我沒做虛假廣告  再會
And I didn't falsely advertize anything. Take care.
你跟老鼠說冰棒棍是紅木的
You told that mouse the Pawpsicle sticks were redwood!
是啊  紅色的木頭  簡稱就是
That's right. Red wood. With a space in the middle.
紅木
Wood that is red.
你動不了我的  蘿蔔頭
You can't touch me, Carrots.
我從小就開始這麼幹了
I've been doing this since I was born.
不許再叫我蘿蔔頭
You're gonna wanna refrain from calling me Carrots.
我的錯  我只是覺得你
My bad. I just naturally assumed you came...
肯定是從遍地胡蘿蔔的屯裡來的吧
from some little carrot-choked Podunk. No?
不不
Uh, no.
鹿溪才是屯  我在兔窩鎮長大
Podunk is in Deerbrooke county and I grew up in Bunnyburrow.
來聽聽這個故事你熟不熟
Okay. Tell me if this story sounds familiar.
天真的小山妞成績好  有理想
Naive little hick with good grades and big ideas
就覺得  我得去動物城
decides "Hey, look at me, I'm gonna move to Zootopia...
食肉和食草動物和平相處  還一起唱山歌
where predators and prey live in harmony and sing Kumbaya!"
結果呢  哎呀  他們關係並不好
Only to find, whoopsie, we don't all get along.
做大城市警察的夢想
And that dream of becoming a big city cop,
哎呀呀  成了交通協管
double whoopsie, she's a meter maid.
還有哎呀呀呀
And whoopsie number three-sie,
沒人關心她和她的夢想
no one cares about her or her dreams.
夢想很快就破滅了
And soon enough those dreams die,
然後身體和精神都消沉下去
and our bunny sinks into emotional and literal squalor
只能住在橋洞裡
living in a box under a bridge.
終於發現自己只能選擇回家
Till finally she has no choice but to go back home
夾著自己那條
with that cute fuzzy wuzzy
毛茸茸的小尾巴  變成了
little tail between her legs to become...
你是兔窩鎮的  對吧
You're from Bunnyburrow, is that what you said?
種胡蘿蔔的農民
So how about a carrot farmer?
聽著不錯吧
That sound about right?
小心點  不然就不止是你的夢想被碾碎了
Be careful now, or it won't just be your dreams getting crushed.
沒人能告訴我做什麼不做什麼
No one tells me what I can or can't be.
尤其是個沒膽量的混球
Especially not some jerk who never had the guts to
只知道智取爪子冰棍
try to be anything more than a Pawpsicle hustler.
好了
All right, look.
大家來到動物城
Everyone comes to Zootopia
覺得能成就無限可能
thinking they can be anything they want.
其實不行  你只能成為自己
Well, you can't. You can only be what you are.
狐狸狡猾  兔子蠢
Sly fox. Dumb bunny.
我不蠢
I'm not a dumb bunny.
好吧  這也不是濕水泥
Right. And that's not wet cement.
你做不了真正的警察的
You'll never be a real cop.
做交通協管倒是挺不錯
You're a cute meter maid, though.
沒準能做督察員呢  加油
Maybe a supervisor one day. Hang in there.
爸爸媽媽
一人份胡蘿蔔
-爸爸媽媽  -看她  親愛的
- Oh, hey, it's my parents! - Oh, there she is! Hi, Sweetheart!
你好啊  厲害的朱迪
Hey there, Jude the Dude.
第一天做警察怎麼樣
How was your first day on the force?
-可棒了  -跟想的一樣嗎
- It was real great! - Yeah? Everything you ever hoped?
當然了  還有呢
Absolutely. And more.
大家都可好了  我覺得
Everyone's so nice, and I feel like...
自己真的有點成就
I'm really making a difference.
等等  天哪  邦妮
Wait a second. Holy cranks, Bonnie.
-看看  -我的天哪
- Look at that! - Oh, my sweet heaven!
朱迪  你是交通協管嗎
Judy, are you a meter maid?
這個  只是暫時的
Oh, this.. No! Oh, no. This is just a temporary thing..
-警局最安全的工作  -她不是真警察
- It's the safest job on the force! - She's not a real cop!
-祈禱終於有回音了  -讚美主
- Our prayers have been answered! - Glorious day!
交通協管  交通協管  交通協管
Ho-ho, meter maid, meter maid, meter maid!
-爸爸  爸爸  -交通協管
- Dad! Dad! - Meter maid!
今天很漫長了  我得
You know what, it's been a really long day, I should...
-你休息吧  -好好協管交通去吧
- You get some rest. - Those meters aren't gonna maid themselves.
-再見  -再見
- Bye-bye. - Bye-bye.
兔子  快關了那喪氣的歌
Hey, bunny! Turn down that depressing music!
別煩交通協管  沒聽她說話嗎
Leave the meter maid alone, didn't you hear her conversation?
-她覺得自己是廢物  -閉嘴
- She feels like a failure! - Oh, shut up!
-你閉嘴  -你閉嘴
- You shut up! - You shut up!
-你閉嘴  -明天又是新的一天
- You shut up! - Tomorrow is another day.
是啊  還可能更糟呢
Yeah, but it might be worse!
我才超了30秒
I was 30 seconds over!
你真厲害  姑娘
Yeah, you're a real hero, lady.
我媽媽說她想讓你去死
My mommy says she wishes you were dead.
土包子  我交的稅養的你
Uncool rabbit, my tax dollars pay your salary.
我是真的警察  我是真的警察
I am a real cop. I am a real cop.
你  兔子
Hey, you! Bunny!
先生  您如果有意見
Sir, if you have a grievance
可以去交通法庭起訴
you may contest recitation in traffic court.
你說什麼呢  我的店
What are you talking about?! My shop!
剛被搶了  看  他跑了
It was just robbed! Look, he's getting away!
你是警察嗎
Well, are you a cop or not?
是啊  是啊  不用擔心  先生  交給我
Yes! Yes! Don't worry, sir, I got this!
站住
Stop!
我是警察  站住
Stop in the name of the law!
來抓我啊  毛尾巴
Catch me if ya' can, cottontail!
小心
Coming through!
我是麥克角警官  發現違法行為
This is officer McHorn. We got a 10-31.
交給我  霍普斯警官  我在追了
I got dibs! Officer Hopps, I am in pursuit!
小囓齒城
你  站住
You! Freeze!
交通協管  等真的警察來吧
Hey, meter maid! Wait for the real cops!
字幕
Stop!
抱歉  借過  抱歉  對不起
Sorry! Coming through. Excuse me. Excuse me. Pardon.
再見了  平腳怪
Bon voyage, flatfoot!
-站住  -吃個甜甜圈吧  條子
- Stop right there! - Have a donut, coppa!
大甜甜圈
老鼠家飯店
天哪  看到那豹紋打底褲了嗎
Oh my god, did you see those leopard print jeggings?
-髮型好棒  -謝謝
- I love your hair. - Thank you.
來找爸爸吧
Come to papa!
好了  您得跟其他人一眼排隊
Okay. You're gonna have to be patient and wait in line
耐心等  水獺頓太太  好嗎
just like everyone else, Mrs. Otterton. Okay?
-黃鼠狼上門了  -霍普斯
- I popped the weasel! - Hopps!
牛局長
擅離職守  引發公眾恐慌
Abandoning your post. Inciting a scurry.
危及齧齒動物生命
Reckless endangerment of rodents...
但說句公道話
But, to be fair,
你確實阻止了個惡棍
you did stop a master criminal
偷走兩袋發霉的洋蔥
from stealing two dozen moldy onions.
抱歉  長官  這些不是洋蔥
Hate to disagree with you, sir, but those aren't onions.
這些是藏紅花屬植物  午夜嚎叫[拉丁文]
Those are a crocus variety called midnicampum holicithias.
是C類藥用植物  長官
They're a class C botanical, sir.
我家那裡
Well, I grew up in a family
都流行種植業
where plant husbandry was kind of a thing...
-閉上你的小嘴  -長官  我抓住了壞人
- Shut your tiny mouth now! - Sir, I got the bad guy.
這是我的工作
That's my job.
你的工作是開違章停車罰單
Your job is putting tickets on parked cars!
局長  水獺頓夫人又來找你了
Chief, Mrs. Otterton's here to see you again.
-現在不行  -我只想知道你是不是
- Not now. - Okay, I just need to know if you want to...
-這次見見  她好像挺傷心  -現在不行
- take it this time she seems really upset... - Not now!
長官  我不想做交通協管
Sir. I don't wanna be a meter maid,
我想做真的警察
I wanna be a real cop.
你以為市長把你分過來時
Do you think the mayor asked what I wanted...
-問過我想要什麼嗎  -可是  長官
- when he assigned you to me? - But, sir...
生活不是卡通音樂劇
Life isn't some cartoon musical
只要唱唱跳跳的  然後無聊的夢
where you sing a little song, and your insipid dreams...
就奇跡般地成真了  放手吧
magically come true! So let it go.
牛局長  拜託了  五分鐘就好
Chief Bogo, please! Five minutes of your time, please.
抱歉  長官  我想攔住她  但是太滑了
I'm sorry sir. I tried to stop her, she's super slippery.
我得坐一坐
I gotta go sit down.
夫人  我說了  我們已經盡力了
Ma'am, as I've told you, we're doing everything we can.
我丈夫失蹤十天了
My husband has been missing for ten days.
-他叫艾米特·水獺頓  -我知道
- His name is Emmitt Otterton. - Yes. I know.
是花匠  我們有兩個孩子
He's a florist. We have 2 beautiful children.
他不會憑空消失的
He would never just disappear.
夫人  我們的警探都很忙
Ma'am, our detectives are very busy.
拜託了  肯定有人能找到艾米特的
Please. There's gotta be somebody to find my Emmitt.
-水獺頓夫人  -我能找到
- Mrs. Otterton. - I will find him.
謝謝你  保佑你  小兔子
Thank you! Bless you, bless you, little bunny!
拿著這個  找到我的艾米特
Take this. Find my Emmitt.
帶他回來見我和孩子們  擺脫了
Bring him home to me and my babies. Please.
水獺頓夫人  請在外面等
Mrs. Otterton. Please wait out here.
好啊  太感謝你們兩個了
Of course. Oh, thank you both so much!
稍等
One second.
-你被炒了  -什麼  為什麼
- You're fired. - What? Why?
違抗命令  我要打開門
Insubordination! Now. I'm going to open this door,
然後你告訴那水獺
and you're going to tell that Otter
你之前是交通協管  有嚴重妄想症
you're a former meter maid with delusion of grandeur,
不能接這個案子
who will not be taking the case.
我聽說霍普斯警官接了案子
I just heard Officer Hopps is taking the case!
頭羊市長助理
Assistant Mayor Bellwether!
哺乳動物選拔行動真的有了成效
The Mammal Inclusion Initiative is really starting to pay off.
獅心市長肯定高興壞了
Mayor Lionheart is just gonna be so jazzed!
先別告訴市長吧
No, let's not tell the mayor just yet.
信息發送成功  好了
And I sent it, and it is done, so I did do that.
我覺得這下案子有把握了
All right, well, I'd say the case is in good hands.
我們小動物就得互相照應
Us little guys really need to stick together, right?
-才能羊眉兔氣  -真逗
- Like glue. - Good one.
有問題就打我電話  好嗎
Just call me if you ever need anything. Okay?
我就是你在市政廳的朋友
You've always got a friend at City Hall,
好了  朱迪  再見
Judy. All right! Bye-bye!
謝謝你  女士
Thank you, ma'am!
我給你48小時
I will give you 48 hours.
太棒了
Yes!
-也就是兩天時間內找到艾米特·水獺頓  -好
- That's two days to find Emmitt Otterton. - Okay.
但是找不到  你就得辭職
But...you strike out, you resign.
好吧  成交
Okay. Deal.
很好  爪豪斯會把完整的案宗給你
Splendid. Clawhauser will give you the complete case file.
給你  失蹤的水獺
Here you go. One missing otter.
動物城警局
失蹤哺乳動物報告
-就這麼點  -就是說呀
- That's it? - Yikes!
這是我見過的最薄的案宗了  線索  無
That is the smallest case file I've ever seen. Leads, none.
目擊證人  無
Witnesses, none.
而且你現在還進不了電腦系統  所以
And you're not in the computer system yet, so...
資源  無
Resources, none!
希望你沒把自己的前途
Hoo, I hope you didn't stake your career
都賭在這個案子上
on cracking this one.
好吧  最後出現的地點
Okay. Last known sighting.
最後出現地點
可以借我用一下嗎  謝謝
Can I just borrow? Thank you.
-爪子冰棒  -作案凶器
- Pawpsicle? - The murder weapon!
-"來嘗嘗爪子冰棒"  -沒錯  因為那
- "Get your Pawpsicle"... - Yeah! Cause that...
那是什麼意思
What does that mean?
意思是我有線索了
It means I have a lead.
-你好  又是我  -是嘟嘟警官啊
- Hi! Hello! It's me again! - Hey! It's Officer Toot-Toot.
不  我是霍普斯警官
No. Actually it's Officer Hopps,
我要問你幾個問題  是關於一個案子的
and I'm here to ask you some questions about a case.
怎麼了  交通協管
What happened, meter maid?
有人把交通錐標偷走了嗎
Did someone steal a traffic cone?
不是我幹的
It wasn't me.
蘿蔔頭  你會把寶寶吵醒的
Hey, Carrots, you're gonna wake the baby.
我要去工作了
I gotta get to work.
這很重要  先生
This is important, sir.
你那十塊錢的爪子冰棒可以等一會再賣
I think your ten dollars worth of Pawpsicles can wait.
小傢伙  我一天掙兩百塊呢
I make 200 bucks a day, fluff.
從我12歲起  一年365天無休
365 days a year, since I was 12.
時間就是金錢  讓開
And time is money. Hop along.
請你看一下這張照片
Please just look at the picture.
水獺頓先生手裡的爪子冰棒是你賣給他的吧
You sold Mr. Otterton that Pawpsicle, right?
-你認識他嗎  -沒有我不認識的人
- Do you know him? - I know everybody.
而且我還知道某處的一家玩具店
And I also know that somewhere
丟了一個毛絨玩具
there's a toy store missing its stuffed animal,
所以你趕緊回盒子裡待著吧
so why don't you get back to your box?
好吧  看來你是敬酒不吃吃罰酒
Fine. Then we'll have to do this the hard way.
你把我的嬰兒車鎖住了嗎
Did you just boot my stroller?
尼古拉斯·王爾德  你被捕了
Nicholas Wilde, you are under arrest.
理由呢  傷害你的感情嗎
For what? Hurting your feelings?
偷稅漏稅
Felony tax evasion.
從你12歲開始  每年365天
Yeah.. 200 dollars a day, 365 days a year,
每天200塊
since you were 12...
一共是20年  所以乘以20
that's two decades, so times twenty,
也就是146萬  應該沒錯吧
which is 1,460,000, I think.
雖然我只是只蠢兔子
I mean, I am just a dumb bunny,
不過我們很會算數[繁殖]
but we are good at multiplying.
總而言之  在你的稅務報表上
Anyway, according to your tax forms,
你申報了  讓我看看  零元的稅
you reported, let me see here, zero!
倒霉的是
Unfortunately,
稅收表格上作假是重罪
lying on a federal form is a punishable offense.
-要判刑5年  -空口無憑
- 5 years jail time. - Well, it's my word against yours.
小傢伙  從我12歲起
200 bucks a day, fluff,
每年365天  每天200塊
365 days a year, since I was twelve.
其實呢  我都錄下來了
Actually it's your word against yours.
如果你想要這支筆  你就得幫我找到
And if you want this pen you're going to help me
這只失蹤的水獺  不然的話
find this poor missing otter, or the only place
你就只能在監獄的食堂裡賣冰棒了
you'll be selling Pawpsicles is the prison cafeteria.
這叫智取  親愛的
It's called a hustle, sweet heart.
她把你給耍了
She hustled you.
好個智取
She hustled you good!
你現在是警察了  尼克
You're a cop now, Nick.
給你張貼紙  你會用得上的
You're gonna need one of these.
祝你和小毛球合作愉快
Have fun working with the fuzz!
開始交代吧
Start talking.
我不知道他在哪  我只看到他往哪去了
I don't know where he is, I only saw where he went.
棒極了  走吧
Great, let's go!
那地方可不適合可愛的小兔兔
It's not exactly a place for a cute little bunny.
-不許說我可愛  上車  -好吧  你說了算
- Don't call me cute, get in the car. - Okay. You're the boss.
你好
Hi. Hello?
我是  你好
I'm... Hello?
你好  你好
Hello? Hello?
你好  我是
Hello! My name is...
我現在就得打斷你
You know, I'm gonna hit the pause button right there.
因為我們不需要兔子童子軍曲奇餅了
Cause we're all good on bunny scout cookies.
不
Uh, no.
我是動物城警局的霍普斯警官
I'm Officer Hopps, ZPD.
我在尋找一隻失蹤的哺乳動物
I'm looking for a missing mammal...
艾米特·水獺頓  就是這位
Emmitt Otterton. Right here.
他曾經是這裡的常客
He may have frequented this establishment?
沒錯  老艾米特
Yeah, old Emmitt!
好幾周沒見到他了
Haven't seen him in a couple of weeks.
但是  你應該找他的瑜伽教練談談
But hey, you should talk to his yoga instructor.
我很樂意帶你們到後面去
I'd be happy to take you back.
非常感謝
Oh, thank you so much,
真是非常非常感謝你  這真是
I'd appericiate that more than you can imagine, it'd be such...
你沒穿衣服
Oh! You are naked..
當然  我們這裡是自然主義俱樂部
Oh, for sure. We're a naturalist club!
沒錯  在動物城誰都能成就無限可能
Yeah. In Zootopia anyone can be anything.
這些人  他們就喜歡光著
These guys, they be naked.
南吉就在歡樂池的另一邊
Nangi's just on the other side of the Pleasure Pool.
天啊  這裡讓你覺得彆扭嗎
Oh boy. Does this make you uncomfortable?
因為你要是覺得彆扭的話  現在放棄還不丟人
Because if so, there's no shame in calling it quits.
很丟人
Yes, there is.
這才像話
Boy, that's the spirit.
沒錯  有些哺乳動物認為自然主義很奇怪
Yeah, some mammals say the naturalist life is weird.
可你知道什麼才是奇怪嗎
But you know what I say is weird?
動物穿衣服才奇怪呢  找到她了
Clothes on animals! Here we go!
你們也看到了  南吉是頭大象
As you can see, Nangi is an elephant,
所以她一定會記得所有細節
so she'll totally remember everything.
南吉
Hey, Nangi.
他們要問你幾個水獺艾米特的問題
These dudes have some questions about Emmitt the otter.
誰
Who?
艾米特·水獺頓
Emmitt Otterton.
他上你的瑜伽課上了六年了
Been coming to your yoga class for like six years.
我不記得這只河狸
I have no memory of this beaver.
其實他是只水獺
He's an otter, actually.
他幾周前的週三來過  記得嗎
He was here a couple of Wednesdays ago. Remember?
不記得
No.
他穿了一件綠色的針織毛衣背心
Yeah, he was wearing a green cable knit sweater vest,
還有一條新買的誇特衛寬鬆褲
and a new pair of Quarterway slacks.
還繫了條佩斯利花紋領帶  漂亮的溫莎結
Oh, and a Paisley tie, sweet Windsor knot.
-可帥了  記得嗎  南吉  -不記得
- Real tight. Remember that, Nangi? - No.
沒錯  咱們倆一塊送他出去的
Yeah, and we both walked him out,
然後他上了一輛銀邊的白色舊車
and he got into this big old white car with a silver trim.
那車該送修了
Needed a tune up.
第三個汽缸都不打火了  記得嗎  南吉
The third cylinder wasn't firing. Remember that, Nangi?
不記得
No.
你不會恰好記得車牌號碼吧
You didn't happen to catch the licence plate number?
-記得嗎  -當然
- Did you? - Oh, for sure.
車牌是29THD03
It was 2-9-T-H-D-0-3.
03  你提供了很多有用的信息  謝謝
0-3. Wow, this is a lot of great info. Thank you.
我就說南吉的記憶力好的很嘛
Told you Nangi has a mind like a steel trap.
真希望我也能有大象這麼好的記憶力
I wish I had a memory like an elephant.
迷泉綠洲
我玩的很開心  你就不用謝我了
Well, I had a ball. You are welcome for the clue.
既然傻瓜都能查到車牌號碼
And seeing as any moron can run a plate,
那麼我就拿上筆跟你道別了
I will take that pen and bid you adieu.
車牌號  我查不了車牌號
The plate. I can't run a plate.
我還進不了電腦系統
I'm not in the system yet.
-請把筆給我  -你剛才說什麼
- Give me the pen, please. - What was it you said?
傻瓜都能查車牌號
Any moron can run a plate?
要是這裡有個傻瓜
Gosh, if only there were a moron around
能幹這件事就好了
who were up to the task.
兔子  我已經照你說的做了
Rabbit, I did what you asked.
你不能永遠抓著我不放
You can't keep me on the hook forever.
不會永遠的
Not forever.
我只剩36個小時來破案了
Well, I only have 36 hours left to solve this case.
你到底能不能查車牌號
So can you run the plate or not?
我剛想起來  我有個朋友在車管所工作
Actually, I just remembered, I have a pal at the DMV.
車管所
閃電是這裡最快的人
Flash is the fastest guy in there.
你要辦事  找他就對了
You need something done, he's on it.
希望如此
I hope so.
我們的時間真的很緊  每一分鐘都很重要
We are really fighting the clock and every minute counts.
等等  他們全都是樹獺嗎
Wait. They're all sloths?
你說會很快的
You said this was going to be quick!
怎麼  就因為他是樹獺
What, are you saying just because he's a sloth
他就快不起來嗎
he can't be fast?
不是誰都能成就無限可能嗎
I thought in Zootopia anyone could be anything.
閃電  閃電  數你最快
Flash, Flash, Hundred Yard Dash!
哥們  見到你真高興
Buddy, it's nice to see you.
我也  很高興  見到你
Nice to... see you... too.
閃電  給你介紹一下我的朋友
Hey, Flash, I'd love you to meet my friend.
親愛的  我忘了你叫什麼名字了
Ah... Darlin, I've forgotten your name.
我是朱迪·霍普斯警官  你好嗎
Officer Judy Hopps, ZPD. How are you?
我
I am...
過得
doing... just..
-挺好  -還  不錯
- Fine? - As well..as..I can..be...
-有什麼  -堅持住
- What... - Hang in there.
-可以  -我希望你可以幫我查一個車牌
- can I...do... - Well, I was hoping you could run a plate...
-幫你  -我希望你可以
- for you... - Well, I was hoping you could...
的嗎
...today?
我希望你可以幫我們查一個車牌號碼
Well, I was hoping you could run a plate for us.
我們真的很著急
We are in a really big hurry.
-當然  車牌號碼  是  -29T
- Sure... What's the...plate... - 2-9-T...
-什麼  -29THD03
- number? - 2-9-T-H-D-0-3.
-29  -THD03
- 2...9... - T-H-D-0-3.
-T  -HD03
- T... - H-D-0-3.
-H  -D03
- H... - D-0-3.
-D  -03
- D... - 0-3.
-0  -3
- 0... - 3!
-閃電  想聽個笑話嗎  -不要
- Hey, Flash. Wanna hear a joke? - No!
好啊
Sure.
駱駝為什麼會有三個駝峰
What do you call a three-humped camel?
我不知道  駱駝為什麼
I don't know. What do you call...
-有三個駝峰  -會  有  三個駝峰
- Three-humped camel. - A three-humped...camel?
懷孕了
Pregnant.
哈哈  沒錯  很好笑  很好笑
Ha ha. Yes, very funny, very funny!
我們能不能認真工作
Can we please just focus on the task?
等等  等等
Wait, wait!
-普莉希拉  -不
- Priscilla! - Oh, no!
-什麼事  閃電  -駱駝
- Yes...Flash? - What...do..
-不  -為什麼會有
- No... - you call...
三個駝峰
A three-humped camel?
懷孕了  好了  棒極了  我們知道了
Pregnant! Okay! Great! We got it!
-求求你  -三個駝峰
- Please just... - three...humped...
動物城哺乳動物車管所
車牌號  29THD03
車主  冰原鎮豪華轎車服務公司
地址  動物城冰原鎮755常青街
-給  -好的  好的  快  謝謝
- Here...you... - Yes! Yeah, yeah! Hurry, thank you!
-29THD03  -你
- 2-9-T-H-D-0-3. - ...go.
註冊在病源鎮豪華轎車服務公司
It's registered to Tundratown Limo Service.
水獺頓坐豪華轎車走了  這輛車在病源鎮
A limo took Otterton! And the limo's in Tundratown!
就在病源鎮
It's in Tundratown!
好個智取  哥們  我愛你  我欠你的
Way to hustle, bud. I love you. I owe you.
快走  我們得趕在下班高峰期前
Hurry! We gotta beat the rush hour and...
已經是晚上了
It's night?!
鎖門了  棒極了
Closed. Great.
冰原鎮豪華轎車服務公司
我敢說你沒有搜索令吧
And I will betcha you don't have a warrant to get in, hmm?
-該死  真是掃興  -你故意把耽誤了我一天
- Darn it. It's a bummer. - You wasted the day on purpose.
女士  我戴著假警徽
Ma'am, I have a fake badge.
我絕不會妨礙你假裝調查的
I would never impede your pretend investigation.
這不是假裝調查
It's not a pretend investigation!
看  看到他了嗎  這只水獺失蹤了
Look, see? See him? This otter is missing.
那他們應該派個真警察去找他
Well, then they should have gotten a real cop to find him.
你什麼毛病  看到我失敗
What is your problem? Does seeing me fail
能讓你對自己悲哀的生活感覺好些嗎
somehow make you feel better about your own sad, miserable life?
是的  當然了
It does, 100 %.
既然你沒有搜索令
Now, since you're sans warrant.
那咱們兩清了吧
I guess we're done?
好吧  兩清了  給你筆
Fine. We are done. Here's your pen.
首先  你丟東西的動作真像兔子
First off, you throw like a bunny.
其次  你真是個輸不起的傢伙
Second, you're a very sore loser.
回頭見了  毛茸茸警官  可惜都結束了
See you later, Officer Fluff. So sad this is over.
真希望能多幫上你點忙
I wish I could have helped more.
問題是
The thing is,
有正經的理由  就不需要搜查令
you don't need a warrant if you have probable cause,
我非常確定我見到了
and I'm pretty sure I saw a...
一隻賊眉鼠眼的傢伙翻過了柵欄
shifty lowlife climbing the fence.
所以你還真幫了不少忙  走吧
So you're helping plenty! Come on!
29THD03  就是這輛了
2-9-T-H-D-0-3! This is it!
北極熊毛
Polar bear fur.
-天啊  -什麼  怎麼了
- Oh my God! - What? What?
傑裡·沃爾的《絲絨煙斗》
The Velvety Pipes of Jerry Vole!
但是是CD  現在誰還聽CD啊
But on CD. Who still uses CDs?
蘿蔔頭  如果水獺在這待過  他肯定非常難受
Carrots, if your otter was here, he had a very bad day.
那些是爪痕
Those are claw marks.
你見過這樣的情況嗎
You ever seen anything like this?
-沒有  -等下  看
- No. - Oh, wait. Look!
是他  艾米特·水獺頓  他肯定來過這兒
This is him. Emmitt Otterton. He was definitely here.
你覺得出了什麼事
What do you think happened?
不好  等一下  北極熊毛
Oh no, wait a minute. Polar bear fur...
鼠幫音樂  高檔杯子
Rat-pack music. Fancy cup.
我知道這是誰的車了  趕快走
I know whose car this is, we gotta go!
什麼  是誰的車
What? Whose car is it?
冰原鎮裡最可怕的黑幫老大
The most feared crime boss in Tundratown.
他叫大先生
They call him Mr. Big,
他不喜歡我  所以我們快走吧
and he does not like me. So we gotta go!
我不走  這是犯罪現場
I'm not leaving, this is a crime scene.
要是大先生發現我在這兒
Well, it's gonna be an even bigger crime scene...
就會變成更慘烈的犯罪現場
if Mr. Big finds me here,
馬上走
so we're leaving right now.
雷蒙德  那是凱文吧  好久不見
Raymond! And is that Kevin? Long time, no see.
提到"不見"  你們就當沒見過我行嗎
And speaking of no see, how about you forget you saw me?
看在往日的情面上
For old times sake?
不行
That's a no.
你做了什麼  讓大先生這麼生氣
What did you do that made Mr. Big so mad at you?
可能是因為我曾經賣給他一塊昂貴的壁毯
I, uh... I may have sold him a very expensive wall rug
它是用臭鼬屁股上的毛做的
that was made from the fur of a skunk's butt.
我的天啊
Oh, sweet cheese 'n crackers.
-那是大先生嗎  -不
- Is that Mr. Big? - No.
-那他呢  是他嗎  -不是
- What about him? Is that him? - No.
-這回肯定是他  -別說了
- That's gotta be him. - Stop talking.
別說了  別說了
Stop talking. Stop talking!
大先生  這只是一次單純的誤會
Mr. Big, sir, this is a simple misunder...
好
Yeah.
這只是一次單純的誤會而已
This is a simple misunderstanding.
我女兒結婚這天
You come here unannounced
你不請自來
on the day my daughter is to be married.
其實  我們是被人強行帶到這兒的  所以...
Well, actually, we were brought here against our will, so...
關鍵是  我之前不知道那是您的車
Point is, I did not know that it was your car,
我也不知道您女兒要結婚
and I certainly did not know about your daughter's wedding!
我信任過你  尼克
I trusted you, Nicky.
我邀請你來我家
I welcomed you into my home.
我們還共進晚餐
We broke bread together.
奶奶給你做了奶油煎餅卷
Grandmama made you a cannoli.
結果你怎麼報答我的好意的
And how did you repay my generosity?
拿一塊臭鼬屁股毛做的毯子報答我
With a rug made from the butt of a skunk.
臭鼬屁股毛皮做的毯子
A skunk-butt rug.
你不尊重我
You disrespected me.
你不尊重我奶奶
You disrespected my grandmama,
我用那塊臭鼬屁股毛皮毯子埋葬了她
who I buried in that skunk-butt rug.
我告訴過你  不准再到這兒來了
I told you never to show your face here again,
但你還是來了
but here you are.
賊眉鼠眼地  跟這個
Snooping around with this...
你是幹什麼的  演員嗎  穿成那樣幹什麼
What are you? A performer? What's with the costume?
-先生  我是警... -啞劇演員
- Sir, I am a co... - Mime!
她是啞劇演員  啞劇演員不能說話
She's a mime. This mime can not speak.
-你是啞劇演員  你不能說話  -不  我是警察
- You can't speak if you're a mime. - No, I am a cop.
我在查艾米特·水獺頓案
And I'm on the Emmitt Otterton case.
線索指向了你的車
And my evidence puts him in your car!
隨便你怎麼威脅我
So intimidate me all you want,
就算這是我這輩子做的最後一件事
I'm going to find out what you did to that otter
我也要查出你把水獺怎麼樣了
if it's the last thing I do.
那我就只剩一個請求了
Then I have only one request.
幫我跟奶奶問好
Say hello to Grandmama.
做了他們
Ice 'em!
不不不  我什麼也沒看見  我絕不說出去
No, no, no. I didn't see nothing! I'm not saying nothing!
你也不會說出去了
And you never will.
求求你  別別別
Please! No, no, no, no!
你要是因為毯子生我的氣  我還有更多毯子
If you're mad at me about the rug, I've got more rugs!
爸爸  我們該跳舞了
Daddy! It's time for our dance!
我們不是說好了嗎  婚禮上不能做掉誰
What did we say? No icing anyone at my wedding!
我不得不這麼做  寶貝  爸爸也無奈
I have to, baby, daddy has to.
-做掉他們  -不不不
- Ice 'em. - No, no, no!
等下  等下
Wait, wait!
她就是昨天從巨型甜甜圈下
She's the bunny that saved my life yesterday!
救了我一命的兔子
From that giant donut!
-這隻兔子嗎  -對  你好
- This bunny? - Yeah. Hi!
-你好  我喜歡你的裙子  -謝謝
- Hi. I love your dress. - Thank you.
放下他們
Put them down.
你幫了我大忙
You've done me a great service.
我會幫你找到水獺
I will help you find the otter.
我感謝你的善良  我要報答你
I will take your kindness, and pay it forward.
水獺頓是我的花匠  他就像家人一樣
Otterton is my florist. He's like a part of the family.
他說有要事想商量
He had something important he wanted to discuss.
所以我派那輛車去接他
That's why I sent that car to pick him up.
但他沒能到這兒來
But he never arrived.
因為他受到了襲擊
Because he was attacked.
不  是他襲擊別人
No, he attacked.
水獺頓嗎
Otterton?
就是水獺頓
Otterton.
他發瘋了  在車裡鬧了個底朝天
He went crazy. Ripped up the car.
把我的司機嚇得半死
Scared my driver half to death.
然後消失在夜色中
And disappeared into the night.
可他是一隻可愛的水獺
But he's a sweet little otter.
孩子  就算我們進化了
My child, we may be evolved,
內心深處也還是動物
but deep down we are still animals.
你想找到水獺頓  就去跟司機談談
You wanna find Otterton, talk to the driver of the car.
他叫曼查斯  住在熱帶雨林區
His name is Manchas. Lives in the Rainforest District.
只有他能告訴你更多消息
Only he can tell you more.
曼查斯先生
Mr. Manchas?
我是警局的朱迪·霍普斯
Judy Hopps, ZPD.
我們想知道艾米特·水獺頓遭遇了什麼
We just wanna know what happened to Emmitt Otterton.
你應該問我遭遇了什麼
You should be asking what happened to me.
-這是一隻小水獺干的  -發生什麼了
- A teensy otter did that? - What happened?
他獸性大發
He was an animal.
四爪並用
Down on all fours.
他就是隻野獸
He was a savage!
毫無預兆
There was no warning.
他一直喊著午夜嚎叫
He just kept yelling about the Night Howlers.
一遍又一遍地喊午夜嚎叫
Over and over, the Night Howlers!
你也知道午夜嚎叫
So you know about the Night Howlers too?
很好  因為我們來這兒
Good, good. Because the Night Howlers are exactly
就是想跟你談談午夜嚎叫  是不是
what we are here to talk about. Right?
對  麻煩你開門  告訴我們你知道什麼
Yep, so you just open the door and tell us what you know,
我們也把我們知道的告訴你
and we will tell you what we know.
好不好
Okay?
好吧
Okay.
聰明的狐狸
Clever fox.
曼查斯先生
Mr. Manchas?
你沒事吧
Are you okay?
跑  快跑
Run. Run!
-他怎麼了  -我不知道
- What is wrong with him?! - I don't know!
跳
Jump!
快跑
Come on!
低頭
Head down!
霍普斯警官呼叫
Officer Hopps to dispatch!
你知道夏奇羚嗎
Are you familiar with Gazelle?
我們時代最偉大的歌手  長角的天使
Greatest singer of our lifetime. Angel with horns.
接著看  繼續看
Okay, hold on. Keep watching.
看她旁邊那是誰  是誰
Who's that beside her? Who is it?
你跳得真棒  本傑明·爪豪斯
Wow,You are one hot dancer, Benjamin Clawhauser.
是我  你覺得像真的嗎  看起來好真
It's me! Did you think it was real? It looks so real!
其實不是  只是個新應用而已
It's not, it's just a new app.
-等一下  -爪豪斯
- Hold on a second. - Clawhauser!
爪豪斯  聽我說
Clawhauser, listen to me.
有危險  美洲豹獸性大發
We have a 10-91! Jaguar gone savage!
-籐蔓和圖軍加街口  -是圖洪加
- Vine and Tujunga!  - It's Tuhunga!
好的  我們馬上派後援
Okay, we're sending backup!
霍普斯  霍普斯
Hopps, Hopps!
看  那邊  往纜車那兒跑
Look, over there! Head for the sky-trams!
進去  蘿蔔頭  蘿蔔頭
Get in. Carrots? Carrots!
快跑
Go!
哥們  咱食肉動物說句心裡話
Buddy, one predator to another.
我能看出你有點緊張
Now I can tell you're a little tense,
我就先給你留點私人空間
so I'm just gonna give you a little personal space!
兔子  不管你幹什麼  都別鬆手
Rabbit, whatever you do, do not let go!
-我要鬆手了  -你要幹什麼
- I'm gonna let go! - You're gonna to what?
一  二
One, two...
兔子
Rabbit!
蘿蔔頭  你救了我的命
Carrots, you saved my life.
我們警局就是幹這個的
Well, that's what we do at the ZPD...
這下可好
Well, this should be good.
我以為只是一起哺乳動物失蹤案
I thought this was just a missing mammal case,
可其實要複雜得多
but it's way bigger.
水獺頓先生不僅僅是失蹤了
Mr. Otterton did not just disappear.
我認為他和這只美洲豹  他們
I believe he and this jaguar, they...
他們獸性大發了  長官
They went savage, sir.
獸性大發  這不是石器時代了  霍普斯
Savage? This isn't the stone age, Hopps.
動物們不會獸性大發
Animals don't go savage.
我之前也這麼想
I thought so too.
但我看到了這個
Till I saw this.
什麼
What?
他明明就在這兒
He was right here!
野蠻的美洲豹
The savage jaguar?
長官  我知道自己看到了什麼  他差點殺了我們
Sir, I know what I saw. He almost killed us!
或者在兔子眼裡
Or maybe any aggressive predator
肉食動物有攻擊性就算獸性大發
looks savage to rabbits?
走吧
Let's go!
等等  長官
Wait! Sir!
不只有我看見了他
I'm not the only one who saw him.
尼克
Nick.
你覺得我會相信一隻狐狸
You think I'm gonna believe a fox?
他是關鍵目擊證人  我...
Well, he was a key witness, and I...
兩天時間找到水獺  不然你就辭職
Two days to find the otter, or you quit.
我們說好的
That was the deal.
警徽
Badge.
-但是長官  我們  -警徽
- But, sir, we had... - Badge!
不行
Uh, no.
你說什麼  狐狸
What did you say, fox?
抱歉  我說"不行"
Sorry, what I said was "No...".
她不必給你警徽
She will not be giving you that badge.
你給她一件小丑背心和一輛可笑的三輪車
Look, you gave her a clown vest, and a three-wheeled joke-mobile,
給她兩天時間
and two days to solve a case
讓她破你們兩周都沒破的案子
you guys haven't cracked in two weeks?
難怪她會找狐狸幫忙
Yeah, it's no wonder she needed to get help from a fox.
因為你們誰也不打算幫她  是不是
None of you guys were gonna help her, were you?
這樣  老大
Here's the thing, chief.
你給她48小時  所以嚴格來說我們還剩下
You gave her the 48 hours, so technically we still have...
10小時找到水獺頓先生
ten left to find our Mr. Otterton.
而且我們肯定會找到他的
And that's exactly what we're gonna do.
失陪了
So if you'll excuse us,
我們要追查重大線索  還有案子要破
we have a very big lead to follow and a case to crack.
再見
Good day.
霍普斯警官
Officer Hopps.
謝謝
Thank you.
別讓他們知道自己能影響到你
Never let them see that they get to you.
這麼說...
So...
有人影響過你
Things do get to you?
現在不會了
I mean not, not anymore.
但我曾像你一樣弱小
But I was small and emotionally unbalanced
情緒失控
like you once.
-是嗎  -不  真的
- Har har. - No, it's true.
我當時大概八九歲
I think I was 8, or maybe 9...
我一心想
And all I wanted to do
加入童子軍
was join the Junior Ranger Scouts.
所以我媽媽設法湊夠了錢
So my mom scaped together enough money
給我買了一身嶄新的制服
to buy me a brand new uniform.
因為我一定要融入進去
Because, by god, I was gonna fit in.
動物城  少年童子軍
哪怕我是隊裡唯一的食肉動物  唯一一隻狐狸
Even if I was the only predator in the troop, the only fox.
尼克
Hey, Nick.
我要成為童子軍中的一員
I was gonna be part of a pack.
-準備好加入了嗎  -當然  生來就準備好了
- Ready for initiation? - Yeah. Pretty much born ready.
我太驕傲了
I was so proud.
舉起你的右爪  宣讀誓言
Okay. Now raise your right paw, and deliver the oath.
我  尼古拉斯·王爾德  在此起誓
I, Nicholas Wilde, promise to be brave,
我將勇敢忠誠  熱心可靠
loyal, helpful and trustworthy.
即使你是隻狐狸嗎
Even though you're a fox?
什麼
What?
不  我做錯什麼了  各位
No, no! What did I do wrong, you guys?
拜託  我做錯了什麼了  我幹什麼了
No, please! What did I do wrong? What did I do?
你以為我們會相信一隻不戴口套的狐狸
If you thought we would ever trust a fox without a muzzle?
你比你外表的樣子還蠢
You're even dumber than you look.
他是要哭了嗎
Is he gonna cry?
那天我學到了兩件事
I learned two things that day.
我絕不讓別人知道他們影響到了我
One,I was never gonna let anyone see that they got to me.
還有一個呢
And two?
如果整個世界
If the world's only gonna
都覺得狐狸奸詐狡猾
see a fox as shifty and untrustworthy...
那我也沒必要變成別的樣子了
There's no point in trying to be anything else.
尼克  你不是這樣的人
Nick, you are so much more than that.
天哪  瞧瞧下面堵成什麼樣了
Boy, look at that traffic down there.
問問交通局的查克怎麼樣
How about we go up to Chuck in traffic central?
查克  道路監控顯示情況如何
Chuck, how are things looking on the jam cams?
尼克  我很高興你告訴了我
Nick, I'm glad you told me.
道路監控
The jam cams...
-真的  你不用岔開話題的  -不不不
- Seriously, it's okay. - No, no no!
整個天篷到處都是道路監控攝像頭
There are traffic cameras everywhere. All over the canopy!
不管那只豹子去了哪
Whatever happened to that jaguar...
道路監控都應該拍得到
The traffic cameras would have caught it!
-棒  -哈哈  很狡猾哎  小狐狸
- Bingo! - Ho-ho! Pretty sneaky, slick!
但是  你之前都沒法查車牌
However, if you didn't have access to the system before,
恐怕現在牛脾氣局長也不會給你查
I doubt chief Buffalo Butt is gonna let you into it now.
確實  但我市政廳的有個朋友也許可以
No. But I have a friend at City Hall who might.
先生  能請您看一下這些重要的賬單嗎
Sir, if we could just review these very important billings.
先生  抱歉  先生
Sir! Oh, I'm sorry. Sir.
好了  我聽到了  頭羊
Okay! I heard you, Bellwether,
你處理就行了
just take care of it!
謝謝  取消我下午的事  我要出去
Please. And clear my afternoon, I'm going out.
但是  先生
Oh, no, no.
你還約了動物評級公司呢  先生  有點
But, sir, you do have a meeting with Herds and Gradings. Sir, that's just, oh...
我要死了
Oh, mutton chops.
頭羊市長助理  我們需要你的幫助
Assistant Mayor Bellwether, we need your help.
市長助理辦公室
Office of the assistant mayor
我們只想看看道路監控錄像
we just need to get into the traffic cam database.
毛茸茸的呢
So fluffy!
綿羊從來不讓我靠這麼近的
Sheep never let me get this close!
你不能隨便摸人家的毛
You can't just touch a sheep's wool!
-像棉花糖一樣  -住手
- It's like cotton candy. - Stop it!
哪裡的
Where to?
雨林區  籐蔓和圖洪加街口
Rainforest Dsitrict. Vine and Tujunga.
就是那  全市的道路監控
There. Traffic cams for the whole city.
動物城交通網絡
這其實蠻刺激的
This is so exiting actually. I mean, well, you know.
我還從來沒幹過這麼重要的事呢
I never get to do anything this important.
但你可是動物城的市長助理啊
But you're the assistant mayor of Zootopia.
其實就是個名頭響亮點的秘書而已
I'm more of a glorified secretary.
我覺得獅心市長只是為了拉來綿羊的選票
I think Mayor Lionheart just wanted the sheep vote.
但他給了我那個漂亮的咖啡杯呢
But he did give me that nice mug.
世界最棒的市長助理(爸爸)
被表揚的感覺還是很好的
Feels good to be appreciated.
臭羊
Smellwether!
就是他給我起的一個有趣外號
That's a fun little name he likes to use.
我叫過他一次獅屁  他一點都不開心
I called him Lionfart once, he did not care for that.
跟你說  那天我可倒了大霉
Let me tell you, it was not a good day for me.
-是  先生  -我不是說要取消下午的事嗎
- Yes, sir. - I thought you were gonna cancel my afternoon.
天哪  我得走了  找到什麼告訴我
Oh, dear. I better go. Let me know what you find.
真的很感謝你們能
It was really nice for me to be...
韶華易逝  臭羊
While we're young, Smellwether.
你覺得她睡覺的時候會數自己嗎
You think when she goes to sleep she counts herself?
閉嘴  好的  道路監控
Shush. Okay, traffic cams..
動物城交通網絡
圖洪加  圖洪加
Tujunga.... Tujunga....
找到了
We're in.
-他們是誰呀  -森林狼
- Who are these guys? - Timberwolves.
瞧瞧這些白癡
Look at these dum-dums.
賭一毛錢他們要嚎叫了
Bet you a nickel one of them's gonna howl.
你看吧
And there it is.
你就說狼為什麼非要嚎叫呢
I mean, what is it with wolves and the howling, it's...?
狼嚎  午夜嚎叫
Howlings! Night Howlers!
曼查斯怕的就是這個
That's what Manchas was afraid of,
狼群  午夜嚎叫指的就是狼群
wolves! The wolves are the Night Howlers!
如果曼查斯是他們帶走的
If they took Manchas...
帶走水獺頓的也是他們
I bet they took Otterton too.
只要找到他們去了哪就可以了
All we gotta do is find out where they went.
冰原鎮
熱帶雨林區
等等  他們去哪了
Wait, where'd they go?
要是我
You know,
干了違法的事要躲監控攝像頭
if I wanted to avoid surveillance because I was doing something illegal,
當然我沒幹過這種事  我會走6B通道
which I never have, I would use the maintenance tunnel 6B.
維修通道
也就是說他們在  這裡
Which would put them out... right there.
瞧瞧你  小偵探
Well, look at you, junior detective.
我覺得你當警察肯定很厲害
You know, I think you'd actually make a pretty good cop.
你好大膽子
How dare you.
洋槐小巷  榕樹地下通道
Acacia Alley. Ficus Underpass.
南部峽谷
South canyon.
他們是要出城
They're heading out of town.
哪條路通往哪裡
Where does that road go?
崖邊精神病院
加裡  別叫  你要引得大家都叫起來了
Gary, quit it! You're gonna start a howl!
不是我先叫的
I didn't start it.
快走
Come on.
你真是只聰明的小兔子
You are a clever bunny.
看來這兒曾經是所醫院
It looks like this was a hospital.
還是你先請  你是警察嘛
You know, after you, you're the cop.
好的  安全
Okay, all clear.
這裡的設備都是新的
All this equipment is brand new.
蘿蔔頭
Carrots.
爪痕
Claw marks.
好大好大的爪痕  是什麼
Yeah, huge, huge claw marks. What kind of...
曼查斯先生
Mr. Manchas.
是他  找到水獺了
It's him! We found our otter.
水獺頓先生  我是朱迪·霍普斯警官
Mr. Otterton, my name is Officer Judy Hopps.
是你妻子讓我來找你的
Your wife sent me to find you.
我們現在就救你出去
We're gonna get you out of here now.
還是別出來了
Or not.
他好像不是很著急回家見老婆
Guess he's in no rush to get home to the missus.
11, 12, 13, 14.
不算曼查斯的話有14個
Not including Manchas, it's... it's fourteen.
牛局長分配了14個失蹤動物案件
Chief Bogo handed out 14 missing mammal files.
他們都在這兒
They're all here...
所有失蹤動物都在這兒
All the missing mammals are right here.
夠了
Enough!
我不要借口  醫生  我要的是答案
I don't want excuses, doctor, I want answers.
獅心市長  拜託  我們已經盡力了
Mayor Lionheart, please. We're doing everything we can.
是嗎
Really?
因為我面前
Cause I got a dozen and a half animals here
堆著一群瘋得沒形的動物
who've gone off the rails crazy,
而你連原因都不知道
and you can't tell me why.
我覺得這離盡力還差得遠了點
Now I'd call that awfully far from doing everything!
先生  也許該從生物學角度考慮一下了
Sir, it may be time to consider their biology.
什麼  什麼叫從生物學角度考慮
What? What do you mean "Biology"?
只有食肉動物才會變獸性大發
The only animals going savage are predators.
紙包不住火  我們必須告訴大家
We cannot keep it a secret. We need to come forward.
好主意  告訴民眾
Hm, great idea. Tell the public.
你覺得他們會
And how do you think they're
怎麼想他們的獅子市長
gonna feel about their mayor who is a lion?!
-我就毀了  -那牛局長怎麼說
- I'll be ruined! - Well, what does Chief Bogo say?
牛警長還不知道
Chief Bogo doesn't know.
我們也不會讓他知道
And we are going to keep it that way.
爸爸媽媽
糟糕
Oh, no!
-有人在這兒  -先生  你得走了  快
- Someone's here. - Sir, you need to go. Now.
保安  清查本區
Security, sweep the area.
真好  這下死定了
Great, we're dead.
死了  結束  我得死你得死  大家都得死
We're dead. That's it. I'm dead. You're dead. Everybody's dead.
-你會游泳嗎  -什麼
- Can you swim? - What?
會游泳嗎  我會  所以呢
Can I swim? Yes, I can swim. Why?
蘿蔔頭  霍普斯  朱迪
Carrots! Hopps! Judy!
我們得告訴牛局長
We gotta tell Bogo!
您的舞跳的真棒  牛局長
Wow, you are one hot dancer, Chief Bogo.
-牛局長  -我在忙
- Chief Bogo! - Not now.
-等等  是夏奇羚的聲音嗎  -不是
- Wait, is that Gazelle? - No!
我是夏奇羚  你的舞跳的真棒
I'm Gazelle, and you are one hot dancer.
你也在玩那個應用嗎  警長
You have the app too? Chief!
爪豪斯  你沒看到
Clawhauser! Can't you see
我正在忙失蹤動物案件嗎
I'm working on the missing mammal cases?
是的  當然  說到那個案子  長官
Yes, of course. About that, sir.
霍普斯警官來了電話  14個她都找到了
Officer Hopps just called, she found all of them.
好厲害
Wow, I'm impressed.
獅心市長
Mayor Lionheart,
你有權保持沉默  但你所說的一切
you have the right to remain silent. Anything you...
你不理解  我是為了保護這個城市
You don't understand, I was trying to protect the city!
你只想保住你的工作
You were just trying to protect your job.
不  聽著  我們還不知道這是怎麼回事
No, listen. We still don't know why this is happening.
它會毀了動物城的
It could destroy Zootopia.
你有權保持沉默
You have the right to remain silent.
你說的每一句話
Anything you say can and
都將成為呈堂證供
will be used against you in a court of law.
警察局
雌性雄性們
Ladies and gentlemammals,
失蹤的14名動物現已全數找回
14 mammals went missing and all 14 have been found...
找到他們的是下面這位新景觀
by our newest recruit, who will speak to you in a moment.
-我好緊張  -媒體見面快速入門
- I'm so nervous. - Okay, press conference 101.
你想表現的聰明點
You wanna look smart,
就要用自己的問題回答他們的問題
answer their question with your own question
然後再回答自己的問題
and then answer that question.
像這樣  請問  霍普斯警官
Like this, "Excuse me, Officer Hopps.
這件案子你有什麼可以透露的
What can you tell us about the case?"
這案子不簡單嗎  確實是  懂了嗎
"Well, was this a tough case? Yes, yes it was. You see?"
你應該跟我一起上台
You should be up there with me.
這是我們一起完成的
We did this together.
我是個警察嗎  不  我不是
Well, am I a cop? No. No, I am not.
真巧你說到這了
Funny you should say that.
因為  我一直在想
Because, well, I've been thinking.
要是有個搭檔就好了
It would be nice to have a partner.
給你  如果你需要支筆寫字
Here. In case you need something to write with.
霍普斯警官  時間到了
Officer Hopps. It's time.
接下來  有請
So now, I'll turn things over to
解決了本案件的警官
the officer who cracked the case.
朱迪·霍普斯警官
Officer Judy Hopps.
請講
Yes?
獸性大發的動物您作何評論
What can you tell us about the animals that went savage?
大家都在疑惑的動物
Well, the animals in question.
他們都是不同種類的嗎  沒錯
Are they all different species? Yes. Yes, they are.
好的  那有什麼聯繫呢
Okay, so what is the connection?
我們只知道
All we know is that
他們都是食肉動物
they are all members of the predator family.
所以獸性大發的只有食肉動物嗎
So predators are the only ones going savage?
沒錯  確實如此  沒錯
That is accu.. Yes, that is accurate, yes.
-為什麼  怎麼會出現這樣的事  -還不知道
- Why? Why is this happening? - We still don't know.
但是
But, emm.
也許和生物學有關
It may have something to do with biology.
您說生物學是什麼意思
What do you mean, biology?
就是生物構成
A biological component.
在他們的DNA裡
You know, something in their DNA.
他們的DNA  您能詳細說一下嗎
In their DNA, can you elaborate on that, please?
可以  我是說幾千年以前
Yes. What I mean is thousands of years ago
食肉動物捕獵的本能
Eh, predators survived through their...
一直存在著
agressive hunting instincts.
不知為什麼
For whatever reason,
他們好像回歸了原始  野蠻的本性
they seem to be reverting back to their primitive, savage ways.
霍普斯警官  怎麼會出現這樣的事呢
Officer Hopps, could it happen again?
這是有可能的  所以我們需要警惕
It is possible. So, we must be vigilant.
警局也做好了萬全準備
And we at the ZPD are prepered
我們會保護好大家
and are here to protect you.
會有更多動物獸性大發嗎
Will more mammals go savage?
您將採取何種措施保護市民
What is being done to protect us?
您會考慮強制隔離食肉動物嗎
Have you considered a mandatory quarantine on predators?
謝謝  霍普斯警官
Okay, thank you, Officer Hopps.
時間到了  請不要再提問了
That's all the time that we have. No more questions.
-我表現如何  -講得挺好
- Was I okay? - Oh, you did fine.
時間太少了  我還沒來得及介紹你
That went so fast, I didn't get a chance to
介紹我們的
mention you or say anything about how we...
你覺得你說的夠多了
Oh, I think you said plenty.
什麼意思
What do you mean?
顯然是他們的生物構成
"Clearly there's a biological component?"
他們好像回歸了原始
"These predators may be reverting
野蠻的本性
back to their primitive, savage ways?"
你開玩笑嗎
Are you serious?
我只是陳述案件事實
I just stated the facts of the case.
兔子就不可能突然變野蠻
I mean, it's not like a bunny could go savage.
所以狐狸有這種可能
Right, but a fox could? Huh?
尼克  別這樣  你跟他們不一樣
Nick, stop it, you're not like them.
他們是指誰
Oh, there's a 'them' now?
我意思是  你不是那種食肉動物
You know what I mean, you're not that kind of predator.
要帶上口套的那種嗎
The kind that needs to be muzzled?
要用防狐噴霧
The kind that makes you think
對付的那種嗎
you need to carry around fox repellant?
第一次見面我就發現了
Yeah, don't think I didn't
你帶著那瓶小東西
notice that little item the first time we met.
我問你個問題  你害怕我嗎
Look. Let me ask you a question. Are you afraid of me?
你覺得我會發瘋嗎
Do you think I might go nuts?
我會獸性大發嗎
You think I might go savage?
我會不會吃了你
You think I might try to eat you?
早料到了
I knew it, huh.
還以為真有人會相信我呢
Just when I thought somebody actually believed in me, huh?
你還是別找食肉動物做搭檔了
Probably best if you don't have a predator as a partner.
就職申請
不  尼克  尼克
No, Nick. Nick!
霍普斯警官  那只食肉動物威脅你了嗎
Officer Hopps, were you just threatened by that predator?
不  他是我朋友
No, he's my friend.
我們連朋友都不能相信了嗎
We can't even trust our own friends?
我沒這麼說  請讓一讓
That is not what I said. Please.
-我們安全嗎  -有沒有狐狸獸性大發了
- Are we safe? - Have any other foxes gone savage?
更多的惡性事件讓全市陷入恐慌
More bad news in this city gripped by fear.
最新進展  冰原鎮慘劇
一頭馴鹿目前生命垂危
A caribou is in critical condition.
起因是遭獸性大發的北極熊襲擊
The victim of a mauling by a savage polar bear.
這是繼警局的朱迪·霍普斯警官
This, the 27th such attack,
將暴力事件和食肉動物天性關聯後
comes just one week after ZPD Officer,
一周以來發生的
Judy Hopps connected the
第27起同類案件
violence to traditionally predatory animals.
與此同時  由巨星夏奇羚
Meanwhile, a peace rally
和平集會現場氣氛緊張
組織的和平集會遭到了強烈抵制
organized by popstar Gazelle was marred by protest.
-滾回森林去  食肉動物  -我是大草原來的
- Go back to the forest, predator! - I am from the savannah.
動物城是個獨特的地方
Zootopia is a unique place.
夏奇羚呼籲和平
在這個瘋狂  美麗  多樣化的城市
It's a crazy, beautiful, diverse city.
我們為不同而驕傲
Where we celebrate our differences.
這不是我所熟悉的動物城
This is not the Zootopia I know.
我熱愛的動物城不應該是這樣
The Zootopia I know is better than this.
大家不會彼此盲目指責
We don't just blindly assign blame.
雖然不知道攻擊事件持續發生的原因
We don't know why these attacks keep happening.
但認為所有食肉動物都有獸性是不負責任的
But it's irresponsible to label all predators as savages.
那不是我的艾米特
It's not my Emmitt.
我們不能讓恐懼分裂彼此
We cannot let fear divide us.
請把我熱愛的動物城還給我
Please give me back the Zootopia I love.
來吧  霍普斯  新市長要見我們
Come on, Hopps. The new mayor wants to see us.
新市長要見我  為什麼
The mayor? Why?
你終於功成名就了
It would seem you've arrived.
爪豪斯  你在幹嘛
Clawhauser? What are you doing?
他們說  市民來到警察局
They thought it would be better if a predator
一進門就看到像我這只食肉動物
such as myself wasn't the first face that you see
似乎不太好
when you walk into the ZPD.
什麼
What?
他們把我調去檔案室了  在樓下
They're gonna move me to records. It's downstairs.
鍋爐房隔壁
It's by the boiler.
霍普斯
Hopps!
正直  誠實  勇敢
我不太明白
I don't understand.
我們市90%是食草動物  朱迪
Our city is 90 % prey, Judy,
他們現在都嚇壞了
and right now they're just really scared.
你是他們的英雄  他們信任你
You're a hero to them. They trust you.
所以我和牛局長
And so that's why Chief Bogo
希望你來當警局的新形象代言人
and I want you to be the public face of the ZPD.
我不是  不是什麼英雄
I'm... not... I'm not a hero.
我來到這裡是想讓世界更美好  但是
I came here to make the world a better place. But...
我搞砸了
...I think I broke it.
別太看得起自己  霍普斯
Don't give yourself so much credit, Hopps.
世界一直都是一團糟  所以才需要好警察
The world has always been broken, that's why we need good cops.
正如你
Like you.
您說的對  長官
With all due respect, sir,
但好警察應該服務於民  保衛家園
a good cop is supposed to serve and protect.
團結人心而不是分裂大家
Help the city. Not tear it apart.
-我配不上警徽  -霍普斯
- I don't deserve this badge. - Hopps.
朱迪  你付出那麼多努力來到這裡
Judy, you've worked so hard to get here.
這是你從小的夢想
It's what you've wanted since you were a kid.
別放棄啊
You can't quit.
謝謝你們給我的機會
Thank you for the opportunity.
《動物城時報》  局勢動盪  城市分裂
一打胡蘿蔔  謝謝光臨
A dozen carrots. Have a nice day.
走吧
Come on.
朱迪  厲害的朱迪
Hey there, Jude. Jude the Dude.
記得這個小名嗎  你怎麼了
Remember that one? How we doing?
-我很好  -一點都不好  你耷拉著耳朵呢
- I'm fine. - You are not fine, your ears are droopy.
我怎麼會妄想自己能改變世界
Why did I think I could make a difference?
因為你敢於嘗試
Because you're a trier, that's why.
你從小就愛打破陳規
You've always been a trier.
我的確嘗試過了
Oh, I tried.
結果讓很多無辜的食肉動物生活更糟糕
And it made life so much worse for so many innocent predators.
也不是全部  說曹操曹操就到  正是時候
not all of them, though. Speak of the devil. Right on time.
吉迪恩·格雷糕點店
那是吉迪恩·格雷嗎
Is that Gideon Grey?
沒錯  就是他  我們一起做生意
Yeah, it sure is. We work with him now.
他是合作夥伴  要不是你讓我們放下成見
He's our partner. And we never would have considered it,
-我們也不會和他合作  -說的對
- had you not opened our minds. - That's right.
他現在是三窩區
I mean, kid's turned into one of
最棒的糕點師之一
the top pastry chefs in the tri-burrows.
真是了不起啊
That's... That's really cool, you guys.
吉迪恩·格雷  真沒想到
Gideon Grey. I'll be darned.
朱迪
Hey, Judy.
小時候我不懂事
I'd just like to say I'm sorry
我想向你道歉
for the way I behaved in my youth.
因為不自信  為了證明自己厲害
I had a lot of self-doubt, and it manifested itself
才到處惹是生非  欺負弱小
in the form of unchecked rage and agression.
我真是個混蛋
I was a major jerk.
我有時候也有點混蛋
Well, I know a thing or two about being a jerk.
這些派是給你們的
Anyhow, I brought you all these pies.
當心  孩子們  別踩到午夜嚎叫[拉丁文]
Hey, kids! Don't you run through that midnicampum holicithias.
霍普斯先生  那名字太高級了
Well, now. There's a four-dollar word, Mr. H.
我們家的人就叫它午夜嚎叫
My family always just call them Night Howlers.
等等  你剛剛說什麼
I'm sorry. What did you say?
他是說那些花兒  朱迪
Kid's talking about those flowers, Judy.
我種了用來驅蟲的
I use them to keep the bugs off the produce,
但不能讓小傢伙們靠近它們
but I don't like the little ones going near them
不然就會像你特裡叔叔那樣
on acoount of what happened to your uncle Terry.
我們小時候  特裡叔叔吃了一整朵
Yeah, Terry ate one whole when we were kids
結果就發瘋了
and went completely nuts.
對著你媽媽亂咬一通
He bit the dickens out of your mother.
兔子也會獸性大發
A bunny can go savage.
獸性  那倒不至於
Savage? Well, that's a strong word.
可真是疼死我了
But it did hurt like the devil.
當然疼
sure it did.
你手臂咬了個大洞  要我說就是獸性
There's a sizable divot in your arm. I'd call that savage.
午夜嚎叫不是指狼  是指花兒
Night Howlers aren't wolves, they're flowers.
是花兒讓食肉動物獸性大發的
The flowers are making the predators go savage.
原來如此  我知道哪裡搞錯了
That's it! That's what I've been missing!
鑰匙  鑰匙  快給我
keys! Keys! Keys! Keys! Hurry, come on!
謝謝  我愛你們  拜拜
Thank you! I love you, bye!
-你聽懂她在說啥嗎  邦妮  -完全不懂
- You catch any of that, Bon? - Not one bit.
你們也沒懂我就放心了
That makes me feel a little bit better,
我以為她在說哪國鳥語呢
I thought she was talking in tongues or something.
誰啊
Who is it?
我得找到尼克  求你了
I need to find Nick. Please.
尼克
Nick?
Nick.
午夜嚎叫不是指狼  是指一種有毒的花
Night Howlers aren't wolves, they're toxic flowers.
我覺得有人故意陷害食肉動物
I think someone is targetting predators on purpose
讓他們獸性大發
and making them go savage.
真有意思啊
Isn't that interesting?
等等  請別...我知道你永遠不會原諒我了
Wait, please don't.. I know you'll never forgive me.
我能理解
And I don't blame you.
我也不會原諒我自己
I wouldn't forgive me either.
我太無知  又不負責任  還心胸狹窄
It was ignorant, and irresponsible, and small-minded.
但食肉動物不該因為我的過失而受苦
But predators shouldn't suffer because of my mistakes.
我得彌補自己犯的錯
I have to fix this.
但是沒有你  我辦不成
But I can't do it without you.
等我們完成這件事
And... And after we're done...
你怎麼恨我
you can hate me. And...
都沒關係
And that'll be fine.
因為我是個差勁的朋友  又傷害了你
Because I was a horrible friend and I hurt you.
從一開始你就是對的
And you can walk away knowing that you were right. All along.
我真是只笨兔子
I really am just a dumb bunny.
別擔心  蘿蔔頭  我會銷毀的  給你48小時
Don't worry, Carrots, I'll let you erase it. In 48 hours.
好了  過來吧
All right, get in here.
你們兔子啊  動不動就哭
Okay. Oh, you bunnies. You're so emotional.
好了  深呼吸
There we go, deep breath.
你該不是要偷這支筆吧
Are you-Are you just trying to steal the pen?
說中了嗎
Is that what this is?
-你踩到我尾巴了  快挪開  -對不起
- You are standing on my tail, though. Off, off! - I'm sorry.
霍普斯家族農場
我以為你們只種胡蘿蔔呢
I thought you guys only grew carrots.
-有什麼計劃  -我們去追蹤午夜嚎叫
- What's your plan? - We are gonna follow the Night Howlers.
行  怎麼追
Okay, how?
-認識他嗎  -跟你說了  我誰都認識
- Know this guy? - I told you, I know everybody.
走過路過  不要錯過
hello! Step right up.
公爵正版影視
應有盡有  只管開口
Anything you need, I got it.
你最愛的電影一應俱全
All your favorite movies.
超能豬戰隊  長髮馬公主  無敵破壞犀牛
沒上映的都有
I've got movies that haven't even been released yet.
喵阿娜  長頸鹿國歷險記  水獺奇緣2
這幾部都未上映
八五折  八折
15 % off. 20!
你開價  別走啊
Make me an offer. Come on!
瞧瞧  這是誰啊  盜版公爵
look who it is, the Duke of Bootleg.
你來幹嘛  王爾德
What's it to you, Wilde?
不用搗鼓爪子冰棒了嗎
Shouldn't you be melting down a Pawpsicle or something?
這不是兔兔警官嗎
if it isn't flopsy the copsie.
我們已經知道了  你偷的根本不是洋蔥
We both know those weren't only onions I caught you stealing.
你要午夜嚎叫幹什麼  猥瑣屯
What were you gonna do with those Night Howlers, Weselton?
是黃鼠狼  黃鼠狼公爵  我才不告訴你呢  兔子
It's Weaselton, Duke Weaselton. And I ain't talking, rabbit.
你能逼我還是怎麼著
And there ain't nothing you can do to make me.
做了他
Ice him.
死耗子  幹嘛幫她  她是警察
You dirty rat, why are you helping her? She's a cop!
她還是我未來外孫女的教母
And the godmother to my future granddaughter.
我打算叫她朱迪
I'm gonna name her Judy.
做了這只黃鼠狼
Ice this weasel.
不要  求你了  我什麼都說
All right, all right! Please! I'll talk. I'll talk.
我偷午夜嚎叫是要賣掉
I stole the Night Howlers so I could sell them.
他們開的價我實在沒法拒絕
They offered me what I couldn't refuse: Money.
你把那些花兒賣給誰了
And to whom did you sell them?
一隻叫道格的公羊
A ram named Doug.
我們在地下有個交易點
We got a drop spot underground.
一定要小心  道格絕不是善類
Just watch it. Doug is the opposite of friendly.
榕樹街地鐵站
他一點都不友好
He's unfriendly.
趕緊地
Come on.
黃鼠狼沒有說謊
The weasel wasn't lying.
道格壟斷了整個午夜嚎叫的市場
Yeah,it looks like old Doug's cornered the market on Night Howlers.
我是道格  目標是誰
You got Doug here. What's the mark?
撒哈拉廣場的獵豹  知道了
Cheetah in Sahara Square. Got it.
什麼  我知道他們很快  但我能搞定
Serious? Yeah, I know they're fast, I can hit him.
一隻坐在車裡的小小水獺
Listen, I hit a tiny little otter
我都能穿過車窗打中
through the open window of a moving car.
搞定了我打你電話
Yeah, I'll buzz you when it's done.
或者你直接看新聞
Or you'll see it on the news.
看那個更快了
You know, whichever comes first.
道格  開門  拿鐵來了
Hey, Doug, open up! We've got your latte.
沃爾特和傑西回來了
All right, Woolter and Jesse are back,
我要掛了
so I'm leaving now. Out.
你要去哪裡
Hey. Wait, where you going?
你要去哪裡  回來
Where are you going? Get back here!
你要幹嘛  你會被逮到的
What are you doing? He's gonna see you!
你在看什麼
What are you looking at? Hey!
不管你在想什麼  別亂來
Whatever you're thinking, stop thinking it.
蘿蔔頭  蘿蔔頭
Carrots. Carrots.
這次讓他多加奶泡了吧
You better have the extra foam this time.
開門
Hey! Open up!
你要幹嘛  你把我們困在這裡了
What are you doing? You just trapped us in here!
我們要把這些證據送到警局
We need to get this evidence to the ZPD.
-裝好了  走吧  -要所有的
- Okay, great. Here it is. Got it. - No, all of it.
什麼
Wait, what?
你都會開火車了啊
Oh, great, you're a conductor now, huh?
聽我說
Hey. Listen.
要啟動這堆廢鐵除非奇跡發生
It would take a miracle to get this rustbucket going.
好吧  哈利路亞
Well. Hallelujah.
實驗室這裡出了點狀況  是大麻煩
We kinda got a situation at the lab. It just got worse!
任務完成
Mission accomplished.
現在嘟嘟鳴笛慶祝會不會有點早
Would it be premature for me to do a little victory toot-toot?
好吧  就嘟一下
All right. One toot-toot.
又一個願望完成了
Well, I can cross that off the bucket list.
那聲鳴笛還是取消吧
I may have to rescind that victory toot-toot.
也許只是下冰雹了
Maybe that's just hail.
走開
Back off!
來了
Incoming!
-蘿蔔頭  -別剎車
- Carrots! - Don't stop! Keep going.
不  快剎車
No, stop. Please stop!
絕對不要剎車
Do not stop this car!
加快速度  尼克
Speed up, Nick. Speed up!
對面有另一輛列車
There's another train coming!
相信我  加速
Trust me, speed up.
停車
Stop the train!
要幫忙嗎
Hey. Need some help?
天啊  太快了  抓住
Oh, no. Oh, no no no. Too fast! Too fast! Hold on!
我們該下車了
I think this is our stop.
也許  也許還有證據留下來
Okay, maybe... Maybe some of the evidence survived.
全沒了  我們搞砸了
Everything is gone. We've lost it all.
除了這個
Yeah. All, except for this.
太好了  尼克
Nick! Yes!
走吧  我們趕緊送去警局
Come on! We gotta get to the ZPD.
從自然博物館穿過去
Cut through the Natural History Museum.
-就在那裡  -朱迪  朱迪
- There it is. - Judy. Judy!
頭羊市長
Mayor Bellwether.
我們知道真相了
We found out what's happening.
有人向肉食動物注射血清
Someone's darting predators with a serum.
所以他們才獸性大發
That's what's making them go savage.
幹得真棒 朱迪  我真為你驕傲
I'm so proud of you, Judy. You did just a super job.
謝謝市長
Thank you, ma'am.
你是怎麼找到我們的
How did you know where to find us?
我要過去拿箱子了
I'll go ahead and I'll take that case now.
還是我跟尼克送到警局吧
You know what? I think Nick and I will just take this to the ZPD.
-跑  -跑
- Run. - Run.
抓住他們
Get them!
蘿蔔頭
Carrots!
我來扶你  趕緊過來
Here, I got you. Get in here.
先放鬆下
Okay. Now, just relax.
-吃藍莓嗎  -不用了
- Blueberry? - Pass.
朱迪
Judy.
把箱子拿給牛局長
Take the case. Get it to Bogo.
我不會拋下你的
I'm not gonna leave you behind, that's not happening.
-我走不了  -我們會想到辦法的
- I can't walk. - Just.. We'll think of something.
我們都是一樣的  朱迪
We're on the same team, Judy.
被人低估  懷才不遇
Underestimated. Underappreciated.
你還沒厭倦這一切嗎
Aren't you sick of it?
食肉動物就算強壯嗓門大
Predators. They may be strong and loud.
但如果食草動物是食肉動物的十倍
But prey outnumber predators 10 to 1.
試想一下
Think about it.
百分之九十的動物聯手對付共同的敵人
90% of the population united against a common enemy.
我們將所向披靡
We'll be unstoppable.
在那裡
Over there!
你就該呆在胡蘿蔔農場裡
Well, you should have just stayed on the carrot farm, huh?
太可惜了  我挺喜歡你的
It really is too bad, I did like you.
你想幹嘛  殺了我嗎
What are you gonna do? Kill me?
當然不是了
No, of course not.
是他
He is.
不  尼克
No! Oh, Nick?
警官  自然歷史博物館裡有只獸性大發的狐狸
Yes, police! There's a savage fox in the Natural History Museum!
霍普斯警官已倒下  趕緊過來
Officer Hopps is down. Please hurry!
尼克  你要反抗
No, Nick. Don't do this. Fight it.
但他是無法反抗的
Oh, but he can't help it. Can he?
食肉動物的天生就有獸性
Since predators are just biologically predisposed to be savages.
想想明天的頭條
Gosh! Think of the headline!
英雄警官被獸性狐狸所殺害
Hero Cop Killed by Savage Fox.
你的目的就是這個嗎
So that's it?
食草動物畏懼食肉動物然後你掌權
Prey fears predator, and you stay in power?
差不多吧
Yeah. Pretty much.
不會得逞的
It won't work.
畏懼總能管用的
Fear always works.
為了這目的  我會給所有肉食動物都打一針
And I'll dart every predator in Zootopia to keep it that way.
尼克  不
Oh, Nick. No.
再見了  小兔子
Bye-bye, bunny.
流血  血  血  和死亡
Blood, blood, blood! And death.
好了好了  強行搶戲嗎
All right, you know you're milking it.
而且  我覺得我們成功了
Besides, I think we got it. I think we got it.
我們成功了  謝謝你  叨叨羊
We got it up there, thank you, yakety-yak.
你全盤招認了
You laid it all out beautifully.
什麼
What?
你是在找血清嗎
Yeah. Oh, are... are you looking for the serum?
在這呢
Well, it's right here.
你武器裡的
What you've got in the weapon there,
是我家裡農場種的藍莓
those are blueberries, from my family's farm.
可好吃了  你該嘗嘗
They are delicious. You should try some.
我陷害了獅心  我也可以陷害你
I framed Lionheart, I can frame you too.
你們空口無憑
It's my word against yours.
其實呢
Actually...
我會給所有肉食動物都打一針
And I'll dart every predator in Zootopia to keep it that way.
我都錄下來了
It's your word against yours.
這叫智取  親愛的
It's called a hustle, Sweetheart. Boom!
前任市長晨曦·頭羊已入獄
Former mayor, Dawn Bellwether is behind bars today,
前市長頭羊入獄
罪名是策劃了動物城
guilty of masterminding the savage attacks
食肉動物野蠻襲擊事件
that have plagued Zootopia of late.
她的前任上司  裡奧多·獅心
Her predecessor, Leodore Lionheart,
獅心終於發聲
否認所有與其密謀的指控
denies any knowledge of her plot,
聲稱只是為了保護動物城
claiming he was just trying to protect the city.
我囚禁這些動物是錯的嗎
Did I falsely imprison those animals?
是的  我確實錯了
Well, yes. Yes, I did.
這是經典的
It was a classic
為了正確的目的做了錯事
doing the wrong thing for the right reason kind of a deal.
另外  醫生宣稱
In related news, doctors say
午夜嚎叫解藥已見成效
午夜嚎叫的解藥
the Night Howlers' antidote is proving effective
已讓受害食肉動物逐漸恢復
in rehabilitating the afflicted predators.
艾米特
Oh, Emmitt!
謝謝
Thank you.
我小時候
When I was a kid,
我以為動物城是完美的地方
I thought Zootopia was this perfect place.
人人和諧相處
Where everyone got along,
誰都能成就無限可能
and anyone could be anything.
現在發現
Turns out,
現實遠比宣傳口號
real life is a little bit more complicated
要複雜
than a slogan on a bumper sticker.
現實生活是糟糕的
Real life is messy.
我們都有局限性
We all have limitations.
都會犯錯
We all make mistakes.
但是樂觀點來說  我們也都很像
Which means, hey, glass half full, we all have a lot in common.
我們越是努力瞭解別人
And the more we try to understand one another.
越會變得出色
The more exceptional each of us will be.
但凡事都要去嘗試
But we have to try.
不管你是什麼類型的動物
So no matter what type of animal you are.
從巨大的大象到第一隻狐狸警官
From the biggest elephant, to our first fox.
我懇請你們
I implore you.
努力嘗試  讓世界變得更美好
Try... Try to make the world a better place.
尼古拉斯·P·王爾德警官
審視自己的內心  從改變自己開始
Look inside yourself and recognize that change starts with you.
從我做起  從我們做起
It starts with me. It starts with all of us.
動物城警察學校
好了好了  安靜
All right, all right, enough. Shut it!
今早我們來了幾位新人
We have some new recruits with us this morning.
包括第一隻狐狸警官
Including our first fox.
誰在乎呢
Who cares.
你的話應該印到雞湯卡片上  長官
You should have your own line of inspirational greeting cards, sir.
閉嘴  王爾德
Shut your mouth, Wilde.
任務分配
Assignments.
灰熊利  牙邁爾  德爾加多警官  冰原鎮反恐特警組
Officers Grizzoli, Fragmeyer, Delgato. Tundratown SWAT.
吼洛夫  河馬金斯和狼法德  臥底
Snarlov, Higgins, Wolfard. Undercover.
霍普斯和王爾德  交通巡邏
Hopps, Wilde. Parking duty.
解散
Dismissed.
開玩笑的
Just kidding!
接到投訴  薩凡納中心有人飆車
We have reports of a street racer tearing up Savannah Central.
找到他  把他緝捕歸案
Find him. Shut him down.
兔子開車都那麼爛嗎  還是只是你
So are all the rabbits bad drivers, or is it just you?
抱歉
Oops. Sorry.
狡猾的兔子
Sly bunny.
蠢狐狸
Dumb fox.
你知道你愛我
You know you love me.
真的嗎
Do I know that?
是的  是真的
Yes. Yes, I do.
天生慢
先生  你時速已飆到115英里
Sir, you were going 115 miles per hour,
我希望你能給我個合理的解釋
I hope you have a good explanation.
閃電  閃電  數你最快
Flash, Flash. Hundred Yard Dash!
尼克
Nick...
晚上好  動物城
Good evening, Zootopia!
各位  舉起你們的雙爪
Come on, everybody. Put your paws up.
I messed up tonight, I lost another fight *
I still mess up but I'll just start again *
I keep falling down, I keep on hitting the ground *
I always get up now to see what's next *
I won't give up, no I won't give in *
'Til I reach the end and then I'll start again *
No I won't leave, I wanna try everything *
I wanna try even though I could fail *
I won't give up, no I won't give in *
'Til I reach the end and then I'll start again *
No, I won't leave, I wanna try everything *
I wanna try even though I could fail *
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh *
Try everything *
舉起你們的雙爪
Put your paws in the air, come on.
* Look how far you've come, you filled your heart with love *
* Baby you've done enough, take a deep breath *
* Don't beat yourself up, don't need to run so fast *
* Sometimes we come last, but we did our best *
* I won't give up, no I won't give in *
* 'Til I reach the end and then I'll start again *
* No I won't leave, I wanna try everything *
* I wanna try even though I could fail *
* I won't give up, no I won't give in *
* 'Til I reach the end and then I'll start again *
* No I won't leave, I wanna try everything *
* I wanna try even though I could fail *
* I'll keep on making those new mistakes *
* I'll keep on making them every day *
* Those new mistakes *
* Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh *
* Try everything *
大家一起
Come on!
大家一起搖起尾巴
Shake your tail with me come on
* I'll keep on making those new mistakes *
* I'll keep on making them every day *
* Those new mistakes *
* Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh *
* Try everything *